[{"topicId":"21","id":"21000","langCode":"vi","question":"7jluK2yCxPZk2P30frW42LXzMt37Af1o9s8CgiYhQVMK8AUKR1yh1mz3Nb7dBUUSwucdo0NrFpu4efEh5W6L2lLGfmuCc9QRnZIaqIpBSN4\u003d","answers":["had lived","will live","lived","live"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5KeoZwA0stvbqBClNMUEdjaS3+MUZRBoio8cBv1HXqFY7dupcHLa2lysyFF818xGSUy988nnXw012/UxYk3+P8ZNIxscRaF8ghEOXF5e0yF5CCtZz0szPzYVI+YKtHuA54rRZ5hQoUW15/nlsaHh7j62uHNVCniJ71sXXz46YGHUs0pei4ctSs3dw0xApIaqMaFFusg35VRyUbrAFE50ieoiP6W4miHMaqa1pOD6JMrSZopY7dXWwaMxOQMfmTiPtfiHqYGR580RdgFwLGj9p10crYZc7/18lH8MxQHCnhacIXGK0LJXILWTXSb0OliHd3Hk6Gi1YjnTA1lRas5J9iwD8xUR33vXIfolJJUEGGt0/S9XZ8pncmsVwxbKhqaHo0bQoTfd3WzSaNYLf0Qy4OUmlKzT6xB6cmzrEnY23tfsTvbnhs//HaVPuUFnyzgIyQl0ShO57CqDJE//jRCcQbMK8CvwL+IQBbdF9FJNgK/HaHBPg8O/7q9VVxcWN0HVSQl0ShO57CqDJE//jRCcQbMK8CvwL+IQBbdF9FJNgK/aspDp8zgKcbznN/dGbv20NcFye9WKqjD7xQp07/Duel11M+yZFkW5DuENZ9HMOl/oeN8kX4hxXsj0ieVHIiWUUdbk80tqiu5+O81ZK3dQTtwq1X3zicWkqbhVbbFKXwMpz0dmRx06Cgc1jQDGAEjVtKtR6+LkAfht4G4pdWIvz67YtZnZ/MSLa8wsSHK0MTTp59hEaqEn1Fmx87XnEX9oypraUuzlT1f6hP5xUenxgFQf/Yy1u/c/zQMPH0GXnTlR47CSJqQFKbRll+PAWDbjUosox2xjAPUbdMeuUMiivWIiYWxUJVTUy4Hdh3V6uJ0BNASD5qiJFpBzPf8aEd2EKlmaS+ihD27InZboNrDl0o\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21001","langCode":"vi","question":"pDl6a8XFcdXp30cgjr2VFqAPe1xIaqt1OzEKqTMbNfInxYgtIhzy8WpBtmNPj/MW","answers":["didn’t have to","have to","had had to","hadn’t had to"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6XwK1B2o6qAiMA3M1ev/SXaj5Jmhm9lhvuflBw8YD2lj+sceIwTUl1v8X80OVdhalI9oy5Iq7w057kcpzZB0CBHoRYgGpE2rnTkZrFGIfNSUe1Ekw190mYNcf4CSFt33vyyNpAbG8B66NKUi5S/kff+6oq0Z8qnH59IKiEbvHTHTB08U0QfeLh4QFqoGBPtlvR6BjHSX3U3Ar6PYB3X3mjdJ2dOh84qNH9qis7P9iu2W+R5I9QqulafcI4TrfNREJHNO/Lud11qbqG3cgW8dVuUHvH5+wPyD3hn5S0YRIWEmHv6/6wPpdn0+VXvC1qu8Px6ZXwwLsqczE7nmSg9DbKNm+DfaGSv00ffTG7HBfFFi4nxgFE8t2GDAsRcKO/OHdMcTlTa1OmGioltNQzM7v7ABFXYnGuYgTy0ofJ6sFnZvUWHUoV9bP4DTSOXtC5SPNHg9K+AnhxYB5DTLYtvSE7kH7p8cPWyN1TW3cJghLvqnbJMRtSeQmzqEnGSLVkatNUB6UtA5go88NoJ9RRzwI7kH7p8cPWyN1TW3cJghLvqnbJMRtSeQmzqEnGSLVkatLS7OlLyEk82AHe74H0tmGvmAOqXC18pnfgHmxBNKCfqsGlLe5NIe8dqEHmnbJF7EMHJfyXH9nd/xHbgK6aX0d6xuACVM/k1MGYi/QUvasudwbAao1106z8CW9X5GbgU7Ng2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF29htPysOd+whUrgrCYSqW5s7QAaKDdJz23+MopIdslTU6rgcsCSylj4k/7VsmapeZuLXf1zEZxeNwCZctZTtsDA+Mu6yjC8TUzB4SYz2bUHPsqKOvHo2Tc3WtEzvc1728qEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21002","langCode":"vi","question":"TBpV3eeGxdkzSGEdqp6MUjFApmYrUW0FN9PrbfpNj1gEmw0qmeHO3CzyAC7Xn9tTBydzOdtnzdwVX94Xd2hEPAPLYKo3x4zCpR8MfTeMDM6EbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh","answers":["will live","had lived","live","lived"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5KeoZwA0stvbqBClNMUEdjVjIadmaWUUgB6tNO6GnEr/uqKtGfKpx+fSCohG7x0x0wdPFNEH3i4eEBaqBgT7Zb0egYx0l91NwK+j2Ad195o3SdnTofOKjR/aorOz/YrtlvkeSPUKrpWn3COE63zURCRzTvy7nddam6ht3IFvHVblB7x+fsD8g94Z+UtGESFhJh7+v+sD6XZ9PlV7wtarvD8emV8MC7KnMxO55koPQ2yjZvg32hkr9NH30xuxwXxRYuJ8YBRPLdhgwLEXCjvzh3THE5U2tTphoqJbTUMzO7+wARV2JxrmIE8tKHyerBZ2ZpFNt0oh7JDlrYtXjzH6zElJvQgOAGoksJO+MV7umzXc+Qpx6oEoIj2XuNxQE9CLuB1wA3MRax5BK9u3U6AhW/gj8atD4sES7NT11kVgs4qysSYJ4H80mdH8AA6Nk3vmfdWrve32UxBl7d9IcsCVadgegvF42sPDjKSHh/7S99vL0SAUE32RoIzCE1N39RKddHg9K+AnhxYB5DTLYtvSE7kH7p8cPWyN1TW3cJghLvqnbJMRtSeQmzqEnGSLVkatNUB6UtA5go88NoJ9RRzwI7kH7p8cPWyN1TW3cJghLvqnbJMRtSeQmzqEnGSLVkatF4ucJLNS4L1JFQ7/0iQFIs\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21003","langCode":"vi","question":"+Ww09KTFDYRevVWN0btrvW4mIVE0HIv6ILkyQNR+u3K86bsgw0HEKoC6nwjj/S096NvepgnuSt6Pqadn8VoFrQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["was","will be","is","were"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8G1+oTMiX1dSJkDQnjfpPW0PV8boDW8typNWKQe5utKRuOcW/WsoQXO7oyD5AIV/OxRPw36i74054tyORKrkeBVp9nG77rSAzoSCgiTKf1MOUOjnAF3QAQm8yqRchX5cMpLvMkYQMnye1uYt1heLr2lKDN97xRQDHBzJD/j7bGNMPvzybqhjCSUxLFvgzdHdr0ICQZJE/9G0XoYrTyG5pT/N1tsXqR3oGgcFWtdmwSGhVjBO8uOGCWrEFY/hZork2Zvc8TZnWaB/RJcR1CEtDA2m17SxlfoaWF8dwRay9m7+JwYd7SKrqTyEHnirpKHRji2k9bnapQznIgPHSv+sXqcr/dBa6CKRMK4M5XXDUjpCqzygGXnXoU9/9qvSXsQy/zdMxum9bwQOBpZtCT+1F9T+jM9MS/oeSVTlpUMYMw3YA8Mcl50xoSBXNgzp8rc3CYkM62v4M2K8MogPcKWkgZo5lByUshN8KhKjNOsP+9JS0vqz7Ngtm3Bxp01zEnzXxltkkwQBvQqW9I/MIqzQcn3jHmf1133BNTI6z0XiaY8zZv8v2y2D+sLUmCqgwvRALUSbPowoYMO2lhGGx16iMno99zkKay64QtcAcu/NfE/EGLH9q+Bcwz+9HjBugO0l6NtIG4ElgEE96DZ10N6EIFtAK8uJf3ZxgwOIuPmjRN9o02969vZO/KqhRziYAJptKNtIG4ElgEE96DZ10N6EIHQVOtGvjyuqOlaw8F8nGhSmYOs46wGTKC6iYq01zGq8ywOmkfGTGz8eXwFBTyn6a3gdljF19Y3Th0IrY9eQh6vgL1xz0dtIuGAeZ99/ndZw3HFYlus8+qOSeS4Ufa0EZ+1ihR8A/lBDVfLl3oxVO7rufhO+EUQAuSxltvKdrrcUVq5d5Mi9m0fBKZkdFI21USxEM2D9f9KwxfaTKTS0/SWCZK09P3cL3/9Nd+MneaB8/6IqXw/QCTiM78eUqeU34s\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21004","langCode":"vi","question":"vzjms7ALJfueu9UNoPh5OuiUZt4Krf7HiipbAQZ4vJuNLgdMymv5sZzzjwelF8ABqOLVXomwkAsUvlML/EixAJF1bU1GT+uDvRf/WSxLGmUASeoVu1KF9Q9kdA7utWjM","answers":["are","were","would be","had been"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8G1+oTMiX1dSJkDQnjfpPXlv8R5cIhAzOorA1weFTeXNxdzlAfA4SqpT9YlNBPgVhWf3mwrsV+yUlbI+f6VgFlN32iZp3HUTeq9sve8IRx3iZWRUAtIjVgVuoiVexSaqeAk6CQ+dNqfK99bm8iv/omPkTXn/GVONByMs37bslCxg4MMUoBlyBpa3cxbH7skvhAUVlQPkmYxTZ4nc2sKJvviUw8IhIveNkVCjA9dOZQ4RmLHfsu/AgRfR59N7yIxuD7By35Pkscf4kFfUjBDi/km4VZWgJIqr9RWQQVrV2EDGccifh+GRw+jyJuLOBFKZaXT27aiKl0u2cHFYi04J8UhdWfYx6uPGPFXc5UI6Q+ijqM1F2/lWeMoFZrEHEgQnCnb4iY+PnVza5FmUZOV9dM2zWrjMEW926nPPGwFcu7dZ79MBgek1IafMKyhLVZiysBZ7wd3Eejq4iU8szk12foYD5XFJg5kL9izA7zBpunLwXLgqXDYtq0L5pmfGj9ntcBZ7wd3Eejq4iU8szk12foYD5XFJg5kL9izA7zBpunL7/siqRYpG6i2aMoBxqpDzOjbWXj5KKZtovIG0ZGt1v7p+S19ZEnOhkPhLoexlzC10bh5rWrXE5hX5PoGpqYWTrrmo2Hsslx9zwVOT8fMDISrQGWzWIwa4FH1hs711bvzeGdLw3OP25NfYgRtfPokFzv4UV8Qxh0RoAs9Ta5JYEt7USM7DXFivwbBU8ZN1ATAZb6/clKORo2DgsGcs687k+upstVubWYfeJ9mbQ6DAMHAzj6yqK5qEzGTswuUYJd1b3YFHenWhn1PAq8uonPfTCeN2guY9WPCaqcPrwnvxOsiYmtqX6p4BlXdFcCExq3Id7I6gITFFsygLYmtUhUKToK+wBcsc7pa29GZ7qFwy8XueNFt2jhua30kEtbQoodRGiurbdSLVu9oa2ergy0EHqPRCZ1AUoG5pRK28zzeBEl/GSvuPXO1IWrC1NFVx3GT"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21005","langCode":"vi","question":"w98Ry+eC3l7akJ/0Ba7wROzg/KQXpVzZxprD0AcJ6ttUmU8KEHtNiTzrivjMB8ZH/NnVk0+tV+HijfVgXfXD/g\u003d\u003d","answers":["should speak","could speak","speak","had spoken"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/rwFQkB8IoBX8b4Wm8iic5AfpBbZxsaQ7mEvLk6kjHvtaxVdHgTTfifNImH9YcRJnTSwu3Y5dv4qbW1u1eietHDmfKqK6ckHSkFGEnnGElEzkq4ORi0RyC8dsb7MSYLEfyyNpAbG8B66NKUi5S/kfdXCyiNRzhRoR8xU80i9vpPMnUPN3PoTUqp7tWRdYc3ZKfFQthNcZGPzaJlOgEn1X9K54CKxCqZG4IxEKMgvM75Da1t/IN2fP7GkcSxtPSDHbJufPCOpea06gtNGScqi8T30GU8MjaV/yHcS/jo9L74FQR4GnBWezqAnJ6Pe1JPz8YWOcYq4s6GAzV188fY9/tyDw/Pfc7fyVrE5mZbxuN7pMB4+PzoteV+tMhn+vmZqZZs0XfFQ4BxArtDP4a0gaFm0Ib6v8teRqUNK2miuzVbo2S8oZvkTt1UXgyO8Chknb0ZYkxBHUFlqC/OfEy3nFfxxqXJro7y/kX5zNTCj0MlLPsEJQi256ctm+hbD7+r9oSqhXnrLBvIDQ1cc2ESHhbGQzLY7FOtzzoM81yHdivvHAq40o2S3SGhbAhjXTYL3aj/0WBHKjwKbrej+PBbtopk2ec20iOPM7dmRWSFBYFf5cSVMKIunuTjkMKwHsAFQaugCUzKrArWtk6cNqeIohe3HUN0SJdINW2KmZi1WLVRNoVBSlJmpUrxdWNG6mIeZdEgo4okPJaZRdQFJeJ3mSTlC4cLXEzI30Qg5DnZGlvNKCNI+JqNuYHXmvKRYlLl5dbS1JycQlCFIWIUch4RMkEf5P0SSzlFWDjd2PyDsBRawF6vri1yR6cMC1lJY0C7tXWEUsaloI4zC7RfOwuEk/FTbsCVrX7GsuvYZUiPOE5F580m6NiGgL+leaBaoaZbQJdtmFKWo46r3Z/8J/xLlb/i0Z4ejPxgwCnEMKXY+CnhOu0+sq2KhzioZ5wE3xd8NS5WE0rPfAjcM+lYnzh/0RJRaOcyaAoHq9U3n48nIX6b9UPa6ktDcqgwdLj6uC5OFu+lmNGQD0QYpFFjTa5D1J6EqTjVmAkFdtnTN8PqbiJyfcxRsbaH6ywso1DOqe/+dlR7AljSboR4qCU/bAFbUJeEqTjVmAkFdtnTN8PqbiJyLRRL3Qwz6wc61whA24qsUbp8O1Uk/neXDOtZm4nhwoE\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21006","langCode":"vi","question":"Q9LO2BAJ8VqodWyfsfMo4YOhOiXxm/7ncymHJJB9kq2hxAT6YVUSiWLtEmECX0HDXIEx7wfqHww/L24O/R/vvlSAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d","answers":["gone","should go","could go","go"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+h8SxOVWE+MdazViOc7KFz2TZanaiCRtlDpG+gISoWWwJYmsvgd5UxxAsE3N1n9nzv0AT7Qby/oM8pe48wpH82Zft3jwXi67qJGQkSbLqn6dBwkJ9oAtY2iOdWmmqnxi3eDFodWOysn5GZxzvY0L+b7u79D8m9cQr9nN/ahtr81Cr4zak1dWAjO66Kwjmh/RUwdPFNEH3i4eEBaqBgT7Zb0egYx0l91NwK+j2Ad195o3SdnTofOKjR/aorOz/YrtlvkeSPUKrpWn3COE63zURCRzTvy7nddam6ht3IFvHVblB7x+fsD8g94Z+UtGESFhJh7+v+sD6XZ9PlV7wtarvD8emV8MC7KnMxO55koPQ2yjZvg32hkr9NH30xuxwXxRYuJ8YBRPLdhgwLEXCjvzh3THE5U2tTphoqJbTUMzO7+wARV2JxrmIE8tKHyerBZ2Z+KFTU36KedCpUPQMOYto2WG47WUr52ofkZ4PAm5AhyoKhoeQR23Ed56dKbeGpQujQ8sECNVjQe7gS4XO9XGW2bBZdjXgvx6NpASPk+vLMEydcJa0UTQzULKywaBZKJc80M4GsHf3J2G8hbAO4ZXCvzNAawwhuzC3aMdn5H+U58SJ/hxb/GqcyrVwFqPKNSMW/jjAzyi4cFys89AIKnJb1xFL2Z4AheUpd4hFiTYxaOJV6i04h4LJouSGtWrJdB4MHc/cdOp4oCq/g0krYs3N2cuqTERPZTPNXvZ71axGpfzs5367fLLy3cCtBZ1RaxqzXlHaEicFmmI3KNVR6fQSAolpy0n9Gc5vHIE0Mk3unoh/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8UvsOgoBjH7VqcZuBDH0NAXgjDOEqkQsB4NpQE4E4wk8nF96AWjnX2+rjgWIm30nHH/4ypYALsDK27rd8vMzRAdCniRKYY+PVgmKcp0+PXRlj9ZdWi3hnF9285R4fDEmTnqWG16TLZJtKsQ5RDRgYH9G/zY+yt7XEjm4X/lX4t/i0ZI8Or6zXPh4PBBqTXRD7PR4PSvgJ4cWAeQ0y2Lb0hO5B+6fHD1sjdU1t3CYIS76p2yTEbUnkJs6hJxki1ZGrTVAelLQOYKPPDaCfUUc8CO5B+6fHD1sjdU1t3CYIS76p2yTEbUnkJs6hJxki1ZGrReLnCSzUuC9SRUO/9IkBSL"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21007","langCode":"vi","question":"af/5fDZKnT0xSHgcfpA4SqKTSJeN0sWys2/SLDsKkvsNQ/LG2aPE7x4a76GgnNZzoADpQLzI1Ttzg8jrPrhSOrAFSFe8iaNCKaxJ5aAmSuo7S/ms/PQ52PaoWb8e9C7G","answers":["would have","had had","had","have"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwGWlSshmRHRY975kyYOFRo8eJPaRQoCLbBeMVz8AVWDTCx/+vVX4ho2zKI/wQiVMwU0hYe0ZckG8cZbJ/5Hv+xXiEOrKibQwLU4xyQRNrdWS6pgA1zZxMmmAONm0Ol6Ay8h8ZbtFtmOfgF4TxAHxvGGYmN7eStz5Rww74Aj8CbpydZAnvVCsuO/18jp+DNH5x+LPqY6YLOPeMt1w2HmIEXC1lNCHMmKeA5NeaDeJum9OhUgWgU2Ih5XxBGJ2W4OmCHi8wD1ac2SYo7ZtMufZYlIoae1hHj62icUCBJ4golITrgySpISOJXOMiyRt7/Y2xnXi46ivJZbTllS1PDRkHBMqeCyQOTLbJMBEns/1lLv7z6J8xEIDBSaLwAnIw/DkQz4cBx9NzLypDAqtzYc9fKbN6vQsgg37G1vTFKjWvJjIqStQD2RLqZkHh87CiXigquU9XXSZD3IIS4wmNK9pZ/+EVKFbW4unAr6UD9SQXsBxkwjBs28XeCyl2zEkm5HRY07yzL+XIpgK/mVeVS0gdP+EVKFbW4unAr6UD9SQXsBkEoMS6IB0LGl0LO0nU7SIpirCTbXBJlKPwxDQ2Bwc2vmAOqXC18pnfgHmxBNKCfqmgHSXyN5Zg1BuWPc3FrDBQHRf3rAhX/KeaI8YWb6yHyx7p8Dzrb1MxezEOCbWRYG6u9WUqMO+LfeI54TXs80sbgidrOIBdvCILTjvO7DVdVnDL4L3+NwusIxfj01rc7iSTgo5UbdZXYWDwkI6+kqCrBXR/rDPwsd2sKs3a3+fdgLvJc9uoS3XWWv2qRkxWauGhg9g7cLJX8O86ATAhjp6Ksqa76vqijGK1B6Y1N2zM+fqMJhoAJUdri/qgDIUU/A/t9IbgbAThBzCINqAkr/Cfwu/GbPPUzA0UXZr8UQgqk7WBuS7bEL5tIRPiYkO3uGwWGiCL2Fm9DbFWO++/eobVSAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21008","langCode":"vi","question":"af/5fDZKnT0xSHgcfpA4SsaaLO4gnNvK3c7PahFGMefCMhIXEQPIGaAMlMtPfuZoO5Yld5U0vATx1lMfy+t/FKsbB6A3tjviU6dX+pBaRmQx/whQn70axGH46Shki+7b","answers":["had known","know","would know","knew"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE0JcSnx587lc+WDFzfHVm5SA15+xvBQvzog2OIFYnJuAfkOeM8y5S+2Em8C8R5OqmoYrvM9/FhA5tS7WzX6nv5NEnJMZybikkAVs9A7uniVcYKEQB67dab8xOAOGPkAmCPu7v0Pyb1xCv2c39qG2vzUKvjNqTV1YCM7rorCOaH9FTB08U0QfeLh4QFqoGBPtlvR6BjHSX3U3Ar6PYB3X3mjdJ2dOh84qNH9qis7P9iu2W+R5I9QqulafcI4TrfNREJHNO/Lud11qbqG3cgW8dVuUHvH5+wPyD3hn5S0YRIWEmHv6/6wPpdn0+VXvC1qu8Px6ZXwwLsqczE7nmSg9DbKNm+DfaGSv00ffTG7HBfFFi4nxgFE8t2GDAsRcKO/OHdMcTlTa1OmGioltNQzM7v7ABFXYnGuYgTy0ofJ6sFnZpgxxzenXlregEyF3cwGfRm+ab0OI54ngYvSzfwz/hMoLwgK+Eo7X+w4raj/3saUjeHrX5dz+X5V3dV+KD5SBfkAXB8dKyHA028phD1dlQdILwgK+Eo7X+w4raj/3saUjeHrX5dz+X5V3dV+KD5SBfneFORLGIKm55F+bxoGA/Vg2hUFKUmalSvF1Y0bqYh5l0SCjiiQ8lplF1AUl4neZJJyg3v3iBSakTjAs2Y6p042BDW5pUlmSS7X22L5S0oJqsbgAlTP5NTBmIv0FL2rLnV6pz+gGB2L/ze9kueu3yFBPQIfKnnB3noHtOg61xLDgQOsrcP6GBkO4eZ78DBKEo4VPETTGbYr9aS2RSK8DXrQWw/KzArdgC+5Qj+au/j/NFaCFLVwxYG+IwxWULImTe3Aa5Tadnb0w1UJzj/D8g8THAF+y5WJSY5Od3V8TS/gyUV2IBACo82ZIIXXxRWlzK36Lwx10oaZsZu4R3COnO37XiKAH/MhTWnVK6QJ07TyoRYdcCcE1wh7Cj3BAKyjUeQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21009","langCode":"vi","question":"fsqZ3/rL/Vjwv95c62+WlDtbgGUuU2wwd/lX6rWDQNoncnxNmi1MgF6dpYqezLtFV10n18pvfnCbq46d6QJ8jA\u003d\u003d","answers":["don’t participate","wouldn’t participate","didn\u0027t participate","hadn’t participated"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4lfJ/a5RBcbIDfTMk0vgzYX43dgGAYcJE9+PTjAcG3+miX7/hTSdEectOuEKAfsj5tXzJcmIr5BfWGArva4iY6MV8Qq6HI+ayVGTZ7+wXhDFZ/ebCuxX7JSVsj5/pWAWXdO4Sm55erdULoojKCyaqNEEIAmpL3xIffXDr7uWiPCwDkfVdRv1iKLp01+xp8pOEdqYFPK0NVESBhEbsKesWTuvRgw4nxm9bqnOr//oTn3ydcJa0UTQzULKywaBZKJc/I7tRJiatnwcpnhULyJoHCPUV1Rtz1nyRti2qpO7v7p0+uE+c7He/8gEKNQj3ryhC1UjZKJW1DoBRLlN52wxQGpYOxGi3gtQ9uxy4E3RcLEsEjKQrvBt2SLSS5akufrEiUKqocU6OQgJmdJWkFnwfaukIFvfZUFZv1ASC5zLg1mc4+ivenqnz1Urb6pDsphqF0ZdCQMG7tKzSnl/YMp1DjJVXYM4e97ezF+xwgYhkDaJCXRKE7nsKoMkT/+NEJxBswrwK/Av4hAFt0X0Uk2Ar8docE+Dw7/ur1VXFxY3QdVJCXRKE7nsKoMkT/+NEJxBswrwK/Av4hAFt0X0Uk2Ar8TEmVP7dM/vVHcDJR1onSEY1iPMvG3TZfEoSsHyEHSafxWx+m0/FFAWqb1QDlKvkT3JASTvNXmMRfpmHMg3Fq2DWzgtKLiOJMwB4pMqqvc0IENbmlSWZJLtfbYvlLSgmqxuACVM/k1MGYi/QUvasudXqnP6AYHYv/N72S567fIUE9Ah8qecHeege06DrXEsODes9PIQ07+r2wgxsvOGTu8bmJXBXdlq+rRb7k4firfhINV/UQrAHy05rSKIEwPTF/ykJ8dI0ElU4a6s3n5Va2S4erm5lf+7yWqcA+0Xm51edEKQhD0ILoneOOHtVhYW+9n4sfZ9qtJxp5nUBBkb0rw"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21010","langCode":"vi","question":"EDOfoX439tbTqQiE5TiCJn1K/pr6TUv/y34i9n6cc8bXI1kpfmf2bt0GQ4+/ueoXM3loDrDiNwk+lkjc30rhCP9iJcLhHTFGAautZATNUFU\u003d","answers":["studied","had studied","would study","could study"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE71SuhifDvTcsz35yODnpAEIpKF4OoKvFUzau4+hN8PNtaxVdHgTTfifNImH9YcRJlgUx7CPOQVDEXeyIKQzmt6MEkku+GsNqH9oNPIMlp6HrDWstlhireg0Feh/Wz5OqMpLwQlQY3TbQbjsr0Qnf+hJRSYxSfosgQYs/p0yU1F2X5LMGvHlq8ds8kwLhaVshjRpAZt5Fkl9XSHM3S+MvziJlZFQC0iNWBW6iJV7FJqpsfNMWYJ60uOKnC9qibE2QnV10gDMdVPTn4gNJKPG0Ku58WTHO4LLEOoq9ZOYbUUkEY7Fo/YdUBGt7HQR93pcoWMhD8DteZggh5rquz5bBsN7zvtBrv7SluNZ65dld+DxJw+6g0RRkIHVgTmVfGfzTlWQJ8DnN3GTh/96X9QqQwwoSgT8r6ZxJ+3RzRrzTlf2e12w++yynxiMsQC/8dKS8jkLGjf9nndsyw1gP6tSvUE+tung78/FPanXe/hNih0dPNi0pbqdNGUHQX1rNpW8fGe/TAYHpNSGnzCsoS1WYsrAWe8HdxHo6uIlPLM5Ndn6GA+VxSYOZC/YswO8wabpy5dP9raOEkcs4Y4gCqJ3hQNUewJY0m6EeKglP2wBW1CXhKk41ZgJBXbZ0zfD6m4icjwbnrn9DicWPfRfEPgcSCSY8rrLQKDYKXIlwz42GzfbkJkyfv/HW64kfjCuYOPzB5O4NPwEEU6sn1kto+KECGGAgukDupWtw9WLdFS4hsHQZo0z6wkgKKBS1PMuWTN/IYcenjj/tv5c/gvir+vkGUT5dzy6iYcxt3+SBIhLyJqLpz0dmRx06Cgc1jQDGAEjVtKtR6+LkAfht4G4pdWIvz5eqw5ILrK5otA+LjQ5XbravBpQF6dXdiFrjoemK7jb/k8VyxqG15oI6PoAQVYj7dnbS0Z1/2IwbRketWScvhnbM5nIrAEwHelQBv3cP8qW04NGWjb21UWlq6h3flNjO4La9vyXzuiiaTgEMCWiyNC39T3lQacuXnWtUMqY2JSxqrC9KjNY7YIBwcMq3/DptIs\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21011","langCode":"vi","question":"w98Ry+eC3l7akJ/0Ba7wRPqiuMgKNgun4gywcBKGVPrS9zKTHd8UkoEUzKtay8KZgkIs4I5Fx+Wshu2m4h5377dxEi9ImNBEkYB03TWXSUg\u003d","answers":["eat","hadn’t eaten","could eat","ate"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEyUsgCWM2G/qGF+FtI54Wsj4rm8356lhhdpNtShHj2FtAzszGjQoBmrklnHsjcJ6z+3XcZJxU4HuesziTWxApBtjt26lwctraXKzIUXzXzEZJTL3zyedfDTXb9TFiTf4/98qbweUs5Ra3N+9H7XhVIual0/bXLcoPa9zF26XVxvfWVNXq9IrKNo4Blv4Oc7DapzvrG7647xXBitsmjkeM5cEmlltvkjLws5meM3DZjzhFxF/KN7B1CoeRuOovaGR3vczyg8bTesJ5XCIiWzhaqjyZcUf2RkSpfO8prXOao0GjB3t5QChTu2dvHmQsm3eaMdQ18X9nOUAAT3B25USrmyzhdjx6d4kEhXqWRdtt6LijZvg32hkr9NH30xuxwXxRWAPDHJedMaEgVzYM6fK3Nyneikn/RqKGJljj93g7CzJGS5nYCKoWG2D2wzJKo+UCwb22dEPSOE+a5XyWHtCx2KrlPV10mQ9yCEuMJjSvaWf/hFShW1uLpwK+lA/UkF7AdaiiNRlB3ikTMMueBKlbRrpmFfesI8H0lOwWByyaAnkJCXRKE7nsKoMkT/+NEJxBswrwK/Av4hAFt0X0Uk2Ar8joMDNK4qOrHJj79bTzQUkCzGgIgFQFbZaYsjT/p9olpY1h9J/QVk1Wuq/4iqJYf0X/9XUj/Of63BISGbdArA/R2EuPS8wylnOlK+sMHCl/4gY1iZUVVVW4cITft8jlatxxWJbrPPqjknkuFH2tBGfVEbyLC45t88o5T/EsMQIoyUm9CA4AaiSwk74xXu6bNeJT4oOpbxBcN/0dQoZK/GUCf620pgTyzcO0ELD11NUhPDaxz0Fo/jxeEVbCcKkN51yGp8xXYKVpztlC5E07+2g/hl10dVKMPs7Kh/kKMvSNc7LRyL3uzG/LXkDYQT7N7XLbrGM/Ibn5PQpJ07iA/ZM+CVexPG9fpYhxtyZdrEN7g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21012","langCode":"vi","question":"qtSDw8Kx9hjw/byuewHHMTb5gOc0n+uECBvahkkdtVjnmkVbuXnu2UyVfBnFhmqPalR2eC7rN/82DyB5IWPXsQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["had been","was","could be","would be"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEx1Ez5nEST7UXYk/eew8RacDKOXaDAGdzbfUVpCl1KThgOFKV/uq8UvMu9Qk6PrTMA8Kx6aUVW9mlZ0UrzS+5L8HYLlt1wblZ6uYQlTUnkFvccjAG084dpX5nJbnQKLFjpf2BQxqcasaTkv9GeqiQ4DPr8//RehuwQguxf/vnbSuWeMp0CbZVyf/pofjaPnXWc5AwwdrIm0dGvI8FRean0VAXso9gCiRnmrMZPwRwuLd9jt4Xqt1xeXIzjiMmGaJ9lV6y95tWMSj2Z0uKuublcqR+rpaIRee+dsBl97zOnOi8tlwpQQAOQp/amCXup7zim3di6OUDovR9VCNecoQ9nk8ElhSN0Xg1HuIizMrnbJvJuFWVoCSKq/UVkEFa1dhA5SxqnZeBAvjOVW9Sjfh0BMKhA6RKkRuJcic3QSpRKZxQO5slwQugWwupT4kyCBWHWtgOItOBqzbgbtzGoH9rLz3EUGVmm362NwgU0VuubJMCfDzHA3x3s+rYT+mc+aMJiQoK88jFfBk1JdoySPjp8fO2xUxloXFzIyk/qFOv32Oo18CZkB6d+HjALTu3qAdSTaFQUpSZqVK8XVjRupiHmUsqmZoomlmPjHIPVvHv2iGgGymRm+54tcDvctsrWKB+PfApS3eCgA6AQfLVhVJCru65qNh7LJcfc8FTk/HzAyEPG+D1wNreeC/biW6ZnEm3zrk6z3AgKWvD4kc8hadnDq9q1HQZxkT03daiars3FNtgFdCapSRQ2Egwtyfa4fW9MmLAfbs2omI8UN2pr7m6lS/LeNxcBykrHrof8f+abJk7fodtARgtmRTohoPD33iDOB9zcl5RP5QeqfOap/RxLkSEq6I/dNqYvx+Pg1vYsKi2WIVtWnGZMUmnCvBJ/NcRA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21013","langCode":"vi","question":"af/5fDZKnT0xSHgcfpA4SlDI62u2zIZ6N0qg/feHN31ur33tMGbFfKQfe/7r4qAMyt5QSml/S71fjHXcH5e4+IdDb8/E0Qba8z5onGs2sck0zn4C0KGUcPvfrHS4xXYdQoVf0VlvjMuPpJXC8b/gHQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["would know","know","knew","had known"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzHL3O7Gqs2QIcHNHdMBMLXHVyyzB583K+1WT/zQDEyU430nsej/mBN3dOf8/oDwx4IAX92hdEavmR3sLjmPsC8KEYKB+19LhTy1VLMvpAh1A1qt4xoqPoivUV9IiNXlFHHIwBtPOHaV+ZyW50CixY6X9gUManGrGk5L/RnqokOAz6/P/0XobsEILsX/7520rlnjKdAm2Vcn/6aH42j511nOQMMHayJtHRryPBUXmp9FQF7KPYAokZ5qzGT8EcLi3fY7eF6rdcXlyM44jJhmifZVesvebVjEo9mdLirrm5XKkfq6WiEXnvnbAZfe8zpzovLZcKUEADkKf2pgl7qe84pt3YujlA6L0fVQjXnKEPZ5PBJYUjdF4NR7iIszK52ybybhVlaAkiqv1FZBBWtXYQOUsap2XgQL4zlVvUo34dATCoQOkSpEbiXInN0EqUSmcUDubJcELoFsLqU+JMggVh1rYDiLTgas24G7cxqB/ay89xFBlZpt+tjcIFNFbrmyTAnw8xwN8d7Pq2E/pnPmjCaFTQ/Eckj12vwU53/OdAbYcSOuPurmADHXIL0ilzv6RSxMZst+BoVJy7d5lE+Xr0MDHFDb9Poayby/J2SPfGxqC8ICvhKO1/sOK2o/97GlI3h61+Xc/l+Vd3Vfig+UgX41AbdXVMVQ+akZkEZSohf6WGRXHFabsQxVwvI5QSVE25YEy1nw5jrCrjSvzYIyjehM4zC1QXkuKmb+QAAYY+1TKF9/t5VtOZYZBozlmOdK9+V5wH7HapJvJ3K0HebKNv59AuVFUCaiPFQKCzLSzy/AXmFiAb13gwkH+Ri6jscf5OOcA6+Gj5WmcAxLPr8hdPx3gqa6xW6yf2W3dyyCYB5JNNSccjZGFlxkOIozXElVwnkrH0HHvzfXFpASzroaRh6IPkHzVJEdFph4onvYGkxMzdM7Gxof1EWJ5xe9eZD3p2zyvokaMM0eeqzZ4pmz+VOILOj5Wty+HUc1rTKIQTXFLxFaCEh6TR6/SrmvMfYTmDx55rJRWKWHg+bYykOfOyo\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21014","langCode":"vi","question":"af/5fDZKnT0xSHgcfpA4Sgctb7gk/DzfMWIe3/S5A79SIQgDf7YhYaK4tf5xFjOKfB/jCz1uM9jYlFBsMEYrxCSt3UcNKPZf1v2CObNi2RA\u003d","answers":["say","would say","said","hadn\u0027t said"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzbEkfyywcOOCvEH3Su1AS550rWtBxG3cJtXiFmduNZ3OrFO7ssj4leprpSr62rBuXWEUsaloI4zC7RfOwuEk/HH/8iNTMUT9oo84nRNKuseG9LDcKK7+65bts+44al7uM97RWbtKGhVfn7DWdxWU07q+hZybiVSSS1hoT02ff8ntpuyN1IBdbsLGnYHhola4OFTy4Q/68SP54FGvQFf4ehgcVnu2KCbOO9fZAu0k4CdVTxK+aeqpNM4kYL3dWUadrLq7IoZKWO5PuNi7blNFuteRq/pwmfovKugxfXfUi7hS6pgA1zZxMmmAONm0Ol6AyO4po025h/1rEdHL9XLHm/73jgF6WtyjwmCcsopmK7qFK3HHjyoelgBSnZZ+x3n+siCuEkR10M0/lG9cC6wZX/zrhJ8d8/4VmXNcXMO4hb2ET7kKnITmS4eP0p5EXKQ0gd0/h3hMvMUa64s2+geKJeQsbBNMP7QcPCmpNuuK6XwUpNbRUoPHlIZplcnCixxIJzy/lhvUTcdqitklYiPvUkN9rWR25XSrUGZmFPyQFHvQy6JWT8/UGi+KRl5Vlw76K0Y5HOr/lolQDnWOfCXalbzsHaEFEhRVrYcv9LoPPNb/mIXOcjK3XBarvJeDVIKkd7Bknfen2mSx4A6sqYiWXIwgaiE1eB9dMuzB4Y9foZk7w6sdxBeBHf3bHUttb0CIsmFe76qui5wj5a1evYj0RQED4Wgr6tKqebycJKhiU6QH2alpEJuzslJOYv1qXIMw+YA6pcLXymd+AebEE0oJ+prhe3dvP8oPhQ1/JnlvEjqxEOdqaD6ZX9gHXdSLK6t8mVXPlrBOQLh4fen2bU9f4tuc3L4btbpcI4cWMMJUoJX856NuUnPzDXuo8+DiQp7fg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21015","langCode":"vi","question":"af/5fDZKnT0xSHgcfpA4SnogzoU0hdDdp2W2/2bMPFV2i4XfxD5l6bXX+8vcFcQT1DS5c7GKiAt+DEpawO01ew\u003d\u003d","answers":["would overindulge","overindulged","had overindulged","could overindulge"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4K4nfOQUHko2kjutEJOHWzX7XRf4OrPCCLYWcjI6EoLTqnDw/KZX4D1qdHD5loDWuVhhFngXcP9mDD8awWS59BNoXZ4C94nPBeO6F1QL75qBv7SMoSCQW6wFyUSfY+uf6YB11ep7jSoAKWb3fu704aX30m1B9DPSbAzXanKvU7eQF7KPYAokZ5qzGT8EcLi3fY7eF6rdcXlyM44jJhmifZVesvebVjEo9mdLirrm5XKkfq6WiEXnvnbAZfe8zpzovLZcKUEADkKf2pgl7qe84pt3YujlA6L0fVQjXnKEPZ5PBJYUjdF4NR7iIszK52ybybhVlaAkiqv1FZBBWtXYQOUsap2XgQL4zlVvUo34dATCoQOkSpEbiXInN0EqUSmcUDubJcELoFsLqU+JMggVh1rYDiLTgas24G7cxqB/ay89xFBlZpt+tjcIFNFbrmyTAnw8xwN8d7Pq2E/pnPmjCaFTQ/Eckj12vwU53/OdAbYcSOuPurmADHXIL0ilzv6RSxMZst+BoVJy7d5lE+Xr0MDHFDb9Poayby/J2SPfGxqC8ICvhKO1/sOK2o/97GlI3h61+Xc/l+Vd3Vfig+UgX41AbdXVMVQ+akZkEZSohf6WGRXHFabsQxVwvI5QSVE25YEy1nw5jrCrjSvzYIyjehM4zC1QXkuKmb+QAAYY+1TejhlGdPV4h7bnmtYDSBTBlmgtcRIuhQNYSF0nLamyeauf6oOR1nw7MoZUSTqfYL2jDo8CRMhLB6kIj5yR/Y4ZfLjZ2y64pmsmfeStTRuF1ld18uTke3XzV5N4lc1nxRAjWteorVTGmQaAK839YKlENZuL1/sGNQy0zeHKeDNYONfmQTR8BjnLnYXRikADCUmNE4wEoF3OnC9gB+TPGenEF0+trjodDWC2zhe19plO3k2MXidrfeQWhCmYz3lethu0aCOPjKiFt0z6Ek53moAWvlzPzHJjxaY03nA3ZPSVW8\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21016","langCode":"vi","question":"s1DiIBUtaqvXy6K6HN6XK6smVHWNToZEK+9QyKyhjtRpYTsWL52bfhPkk4gAmv+/NOgnaIHfw9JPpnz+D7Id4g\u003d\u003d","answers":["had never got","never get","would never get","never got"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE479MXdNiDoWYX09VVPdi1jDvV/N6QMhffQW7Q5VwUTK8iZCcMslfTwRv2MpstKjWxll+ijAJe+juitIA+vUc42Egoij3W3cWia19sbl8PJm7rq5eH6HPvCsQitusHOJfjRcJAKcMt43kZy5Obo/Jjx7N9GSEGSXP7kZcfOTsDI7BxqQOxQ5fFj+7s/oBavuq8GSqcCi+FVDMAQcDb4Im4nfNzzqe5AxhW8cuIP5J9Bcea9rfhNocTve09ayGRYWUOEMdFRHZ1LMO3d1oMmgOvSdSnRjeU336PUd1FsO6t9f/uqKtGfKpx+fSCohG7x0x/s485tYArFYDbXj7F8fWGaoiP6W4miHMaqa1pOD6JMrY5cFI1cY0OAeAXMJ4ElY/mYdWBQaSn4JAOCZvCcYUDZDbIIQuxrEYVyypeNard5vQ83TpQ4tEjB8w79zIagyI0pgO8c38fvuss2F8vCxiHbPEofHrHZSvcSocZzswFuojDtFXTyNxP04y2bfVD9l/vslof4f9T6LRzyAi9Bi7+6KE7+oqk4QI5Uk/co5q8nVN6KDKuGwmFZkDsxkRz4ccXUKPbSQzv2GmeMyMJms4CLvpZjRkA9EGKRRY02uQ9SehKk41ZgJBXbZ0zfD6m4icqUzW1OUygJugiw3aPNmkIxTg53MvFB+8fEa4MUbXnGf9g8+ZS9Fd20wJ4va5gE3Dje9tTzp26bXpdFPUCHsLG3cctXFolXIryDhwVTAuzGFwdz9x06nigKr+DSStizc3U2yXIYGjeKUAn18eqHW0grmU+CDNP6ib/r87z2HrdU+IzTO1jhvi8B1FI6eLowG2W5zcvhu1ulwjhxYwwlSglcTWiNvdHjywq6q27JIqrqguCJ2s4gF28IgtOO87sNV1WcMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuIOi0a9SwQKzSjt+PwR0kJmbN+8EDkWXZstY+gRxddGJ37G4vKJ2ZmZtjaExbMkzAJnxl2QW398rEzzPZ9x5Vb5J5+7sy4G4AzIFE00rx5nm64uIruAre0GI6bixYdfPyQJQ0AsbageFqq/A8DFw5s3"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21017","langCode":"vi","question":"af/5fDZKnT0xSHgcfpA4Sj/3WcrP0Kx+poCeJZe36RM7naB6no7QVix/JOXYEbHHhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["never volunteered","would never volunteer","had never volunteered","never volunteer"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE479MXdNiDoWYX09VVPdi1icD3OHz0AZewxA8Y9Tw9UBuvYEyVu9zyeLffNmrlBSqQOQx0I5Rsb6Y/PN31GmOXgLQxjksi4JrVdh04sfK6ELfq4vp6FIDcwQjuc5tr1dMM3U09sjcSbFcpbMbufnIt/31wNEr2lqOAyFRc8+kIS5L3JA/pCrK1Oc1xOViUxGY8ZVVAuxW9SE9830m8bcax3tYXS6N8sUOGbZLokq82CwN/yRG75NQVFEyF2cFGH+mKWRFCkb00oSbVWZGrufOUVWqppd2GqTDOzT5DtaBZlReHjkF5kh2idHlun/vU3IWKrqZb0uiUPFC0x77oohmVeFP/DxosQzzf8NnpkffvbO98DQBbqhkNxxtP99AFAsNa/atSFD3ozFQJ5rjAGD0VPQpXAYkGc+lFVa4XiNZ0Ovqao1WWWQ3B2sXp6QWrMgYySEuEkRwB0FyeQLP2dDj5hl/CW1SL29uNy7O0D2EGhBZmLZxzCXcb5dhWgSkY8a1uL842Ms/QBKTZqian1IsRdx0llbCe91vNavAUPaeHmqQiJPypC+LzEuG1FjUFdNaBpqJ0+JKHjqLj9vadhb78xvmZkmq+xNb6LJfitL9TAU+d2odcgXFrNOk6XgzNRrRRDpiBDDOhYFXelHN1oZw7LStqTStE8u2XHV1apSLuPsmNd4ddPDt2TZMpmHQX3soEOoMvphPa8p+JMMngrVlbkL1ZgVERpQGgFNizdXZQaso94/m3jxd9zPm3WenKLqk2xujFl7COWpf9FJPAtWzPXYNjpvJRsXYrmnLs8kkhdvYbT8rDnfsIVK4KwmEqlubPtW6gxpr6P0AXT4GOQG/K75BWPer+9Wjpsy5Klhe5VR3j3dvFCNT/PUm4Pjmyytgv+UU/I94Bypui4ZmM9zyNZ6B8swrt5/Zw6v8JUYzvb8SR+5d1HGj+f/2zf25gU24Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21018","langCode":"vi","question":"sjvEi9xi+QBUt2yZVpagx91N8eRe5nW4ssnZZeSn2oMOlYa56NomiKa9mSIhUKTrXDMa6x1IEpN1iAmoqe55cw\u003d\u003d","answers":["hadn\u0027t lent","wouldn’t lend","lend","lent"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzbEkfyywcOOCvEH3Su1AS6p6U53VT2BDthjlTmEjpHrtaxVdHgTTfifNImH9YcRJlgUx7CPOQVDEXeyIKQzmt6MEkku+GsNqH9oNPIMlp6HrDWstlhireg0Feh/Wz5OqMpLwQlQY3TbQbjsr0Qnf+hJRSYxSfosgQYs/p0yU1F2X5LMGvHlq8ds8kwLhaVshjRpAZt5Fkl9XSHM3S+MvziJlZFQC0iNWBW6iJV7FJqpsfNMWYJ60uOKnC9qibE2QnV10gDMdVPTn4gNJKPG0Ku58WTHO4LLEOoq9ZOYbUUkEY7Fo/YdUBGt7HQR93pcoWMhD8DteZggh5rquz5bBsN7zvtBrv7SluNZ65dld+DxJw+6g0RRkIHVgTmVfGfzTlWQJ8DnN3GTh/96X9QqQwwoSgT8r6ZxJ+3RzRrzTlf2e12w++yynxiMsQC/8dKS8jkLGjf9nndsyw1gP6tSvUE+tung78/FPanXe/hNih0dPNi0pbqdNGUHQX1rNpW8fGe/TAYHpNSGnzCsoS1WYsrAWe8HdxHo6uIlPLM5Ndn6GA+VxSYOZC/YswO8wabpy5dP9raOEkcs4Y4gCqJ3hQNUewJY0m6EeKglP2wBW1CXhKk41ZgJBXbZ0zfD6m4icjwbnrn9DicWPfRfEPgcSCSY8rrLQKDYKXIlwz42GzfbkJkyfv/HW64kfjCuYOPzB5O4NPwEEU6sn1kto+KECGGAgukDupWtw9WLdFS4hsHQZo0z6wkgKKBS1PMuWTN/IYcenjj/tv5c/gvir+vkGUT5dzy6iYcxt3+SBIhLyJqLpz0dmRx06Cgc1jQDGAEjVtKtR6+LkAfht4G4pdWIvz7uMaaU7Ib1SYhwJA2WbkJph6bwekYup26vzzyDs28RRF3CGxEV+sfwRd5EfmiOt5IezQOK89549o67P7wp7OUOxdxtobrwEDR3XRkDp0fgzajsZDm2L5S+y0LFWFay4a9WmW2/rcxJbhn4F1RjZQJJ"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21019","langCode":"vi","question":"GPvtoEHwWu678KYc5SOFVmWIViX/uA10ijuuOUmQk2t3Oue/Plf/m2OIsmARVBTuKHfOCovzGCJcym1vjiwBarUENHr6BFscHe/57+Bq0VZL8h2H9w5+pqBoun5CM/UW","answers":["didn’t tell","wouldn’t tell","don’t tell","hadn’t told "],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEyUsgCWM2G/qGF+FtI54Wsg24l655qwDjaUGcLThos888iZCcMslfTwRv2MpstKjWxll+ijAJe+juitIA+vUc411igpSoUWcVdvSxeUCaawwrPcHsvsMBL3AwooOdMbcM0jbK6+WW9NvTx8SS9neI8jSDog3d23b0Unt12KoMKao4GT3pGARxlMbWmq/55IBI47LhCJpuOI2ryZ1B96uPfIh6Z71Ay+IU4UbUFh6TOxbA+gyfUKEGAAFBBCDcPZqfOuigzPAg3LXnFCX8QkpepEEEA9xiCmUK7TfK20L4wlHYiULWKAAaeeGCT5admxA0CO4po025h/1rEdHL9XLHm/73jgF6WtyjwmCcsopmK7qFK3HHjyoelgBSnZZ+x3n+siCuEkR10M0/lG9cC6wZX/zrhJ8d8/4VmXNcXMO4hb2ET7kKnITmS4eP0p5EXKQ0gd0/h3hMvMUa64s2+geKJeQsbBNMP7QcPCmpNuuK6XwUpNbRUoPHlIZplcnCixxIJzy/lhvUTcdqitklYiPvUkN9rWR25XSrUGZmFPyQFHvQy6JWT8/UGi+KRl5Vlw76D/zhCl7PjZ19ezcXnZ6p54+XuHhtCmvsv5yGW5y61b/9g8+ZS9Fd20wJ4va5gE3Dje9tTzp26bXpdFPUCHsLG10XGoFZeooqWDJTKqIXS9H5B+6fHD1sjdU1t3CYIS76p2yTEbUnkJs6hJxki1ZGrRQ7UAXQykT4N09UgzOM/RYoKuCmAt+TAtYvy0eZ/5QCPMIaxkGO76nBopZJdJhjNTxauhrcq7iin7g5I8kk74cy2+W4MqWguMtnGJGcBsuA9i4uBEofcQI6L7S0tij0aQXLQ767QQIqgAIa7bu0XI6yUZsezPz9qsBh6vBalL/XnB8xac44f3LANp55pTArFDTE80TSOiTqr2P7OozYaDNnluwydq/QhJQW1ZNGS4l0PMX3NKC7WrSYg+SCQ/0915546C31C2R7sXcAG9LOSnTT+hvAuWVA8Qy6VOtVnONjL/gYNOEJgRzErLXOZHV9tQ+KCYOiQF4IKdEC/1GBu3vlC01BbSYQr8Q124uHtzfOgPoMn1ChBgABQQQg3D2anzrooMzwINy15xQl/EJKXqR2mljaCoJH37/w6CbnEcsmQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21020","langCode":"vi","question":"YrD4X2Nd/mQy9cUW69ATZKeNC0OZ8+k0qRDOtvpVifpFbPaIuetLBg+isg11eFQ61uQe1cFV43KbCKN7WGdklYRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["wouldn’t invite","didn’t invite","hadn\u0027t invited","invited"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzbEkfyywcOOCvEH3Su1AS5NEPSV30xkd36yVTy3dAm4S1XxwKwYrMCFZbbGVlx5U424Rb8YbIMC57wklZASc2M36ZCVf5CzAastertiR0JgAvV+QIQS61Vck1LcSwK6VZTFxhNdGpAwsPZOuWP0RrRE/XESiz5P39d42TSvE9DvDH4BxPWt5LkxeLR4uB8xhiVfqFsmRD4HMTLkYraLou5LvNyFurUVfDouYW7LAzU1My/wo02Oz7ZqCHRaYHSv2QKE03Aqcug0Q7EL+01vjvMsVr+m5GBGCsBstDnM6lVjLsXzpE1aba5HIylF9njAlIMDROVrZ8dmuMC9hG+0guCcyguGBk5OIdaJLQqtUYn7KI91fXCFKyN1A5pMBbrdRZR5EunUF50gA5EUV74vGB7dx5OhotWI50wNZUWrOSfYts3eNlVfjDIyW6n/UT4QgurJOxsXt7Pd0cE1+TaCUDTWti2U4x3koUe7UzxrLWGvgBP4AGa/YTeAdsrnQYqumY+0RnfFk1y2NljDrjc6Tz9HXX79NaCqFGfIhYBAyJdGA95nstMKNEnl0uDW+r2rsewzXJx8jJSBbu6PYIcHAkofxyaExIcIXdaSG0qnQTMcOaHclLHygjKgdK9UggpfX7a+TRP5GnpW4mLR6vUjWp1ORicxrfPNOfGXxQXBDaa0/FbH6bT8UUBapvVAOUq+RJnaEKO1Y1AnaKHyL1Pq2yhMqS5p7/8UFry0TCH0Wl9uUKZnogowL9eL/JP2cw2TOtlO8Hxmf5553Q2wwmF4C+/pSNdYjo5aBBbAUpnvXlQRUOQUf8r7OUlewfxrN2jOrceck84pN7OED5FVlqxAEmqVSUG8YZ0FQAtOf+LAMfWmwzjGn6ToaLdfhbPD1JnOBr6OhsM5MhRuj7JWkrfAmtzCSuGGoJ/lBmo+DQWysViG2PD304WHzce5yWeukcWF5KHCN1Y3zLupBbVnOqeVhKia9SrRwEf4a2FvgmYK5gDBP0Lv2tCL423FEjkY0AAihA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21021","langCode":"vi","question":"jYyXSFpbianeFQMgArMpsTlHLaEmQhhiIJWG73FpMs348fLlMML0SCxsqqVJ4HiEmtCVwNydSUPJMwxdBtngulLmbIuwK3JGSW5++z/hidA\u003d","answers":["wasn’t","wouldn\u0027t be","isn’t","hadn’t been"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5vxgPyxYXLeuNRRAMsY0aJ3RUvW7sauaiP8JMB5VU8ViC+voYzRz8TWt8WmW29INxCzM6gWSMTYyTvm7JljqNalOyJ3n9ctVgqebbX5Vofvn+xwyUaGzlRRC1NPyipihQ+jGqFt01M0euvg6ykm9Fjm2dfkBLiYAWrDVjH5b0dgaKIB22SLHFu447rwxWbwcf/x0kNXdbJk+NDOQeYD4jwNrW38g3Z8/saRxLG09IMdsm588I6l5rTqC00ZJyqLxNoQWJHGcmDMibd6zmRUUyoULhuNIrN6waekMtyNPa1fSfdaiRPQer2iZTwIPCMdBPUpg8JwIMiJ1YPHVTmjRD+LohUwnbNbQC+JETzZSjJi+GeNB+z+pbiGZ2vOJsBY7bE7254bP/x2lT7lBZ8s4CMkJdEoTuewqgyRP/40QnEGzCvAr8C/iEAW3RfRSTYCv4BG0NaqOdx4Mk6+xq73ZO9GJGL1jEcGgX1aUDyyZwsz/hFShW1uLpwK+lA/UkF7AafBU8G7tx9yDZ2QuG4iCzFGxKfQVeIlIuf/hbJJXiVN7RK0579wHlAisUq+xW/wpZCZMn7/x1uuJH4wrmDj8weTuDT8BBFOrJ9ZLaPihAhh/uyuIvzG7Vcl67XuUgWnnQqzHhCrJ6445+M7u63fA5iHHp44/7b+XP4L4q/r5BlE+Xc8uomHMbd/kgSIS8iai6c9HZkcdOgoHNY0AxgBI1bSrUevi5AH4beBuKXViL8+nP0RAs/UUWCh4fU3zj2WwAgXQrUl/GEZRp76SgaXIRgl38J56IX6FImH0XPf4PXo+X14Dw2Ux8CwHMOubmAF8l0Hb4nb2CCfb4/kIMWqSTfmDXwdievigWAoLQErq1kafD/qwMp2DQTHlJksNTah9OW+wR0y6XW4bYJmJBJQBok\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21022","langCode":"vi","question":"MxoKhpgKHUqAaAi/GXlhe97e/Xi7oqCUdZJxRxB3Hk+W7bB4GLAHTaA2zWqiYZeyqH4zQGfnhJ4zzt9/MhDg1/mcRwnA0vpzbi30nebXfr5lFigQ7zE529lLIcInwMKk","answers":["take","could take","had taked","taked"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE3DG7/hPG0oNXZxCV8PhFIkREPVDhoP5q5SWBNTy5BZ+clqJvJAfq64IRNuufE+yWLPm5QHxGLj6IA1yLNjKAjxSPaMuSKu8NOe5HKc2QdAgR6EWIBqRNq505GaxRiHzUlHwAMOZKRBuWcmMYIn7tGCR12uK1Q9ZhfzT1kwghtpxfoCLfqDUoTl9QpmbXsyIscmiJOmecePnvRjovHV7tBHELa57RMRJWrY8gQ9tDbMvU/ozPTEv6HklU5aVDGDMN+iQDoI2GMttdXq8rMnHuyzXMANJ4+XyX++3sMeQ+yLFkc078u53XWpuobdyBbx1W5c//i/+ZZn2Bx36OI1AW/qFxJl9HcBO1aue9K6Z0Bv/Pi96SQUjDRqNTVvQEFfWHGe/TAYHpNSGnzCsoS1WYsrAWe8HdxHo6uIlPLM5Ndn6GA+VxSYOZC/YswO8wabpy+y5arfsE7w0sj2Dh+Cbt/d8Eazwt8Q6dFxabgE7qRhq5B+6fHD1sjdU1t3CYIS76p2yTEbUnkJs6hJxki1ZGrTzzoSChvf7akF1l7hRW3CLgFyKfps5wcg5dlcDBcwCnTdF+5Z+0A2uyRl+kQZHEhLNkTKw95l5nES/xfpnnnyi0o1A7s4bQjurPPVThuKT3myd8Zqe2tPhxnSBj0D4ZC+HHp44/7b+XP4L4q/r5BlEsIWcTD2n3YFarqhB3goHDFDkFH/K+zlJXsH8azdozq3HnJPOKTezhA+RVZasQBJqi3oHoj782pllch4Q6owDn+vHpQi7d918gJgqNyWEiQ3naT3BWE/KzeNLdak/Jsd66LlHIcqcYYTrzTrwdez1hqLZMnFsXKr55v1vXT5PrJlOTQgNsAJ27jGHfA6KSPYXBRKLoVpt//BVGKtN1nYVMfDZ5rzSdDgv8222zbh7ay4buR1vl5gIMDXbCQYSpc+xtVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21023","langCode":"vi","question":"ioRXM0KRzAeumG5zq9D2Lap6QRw2e39MJ9erJ9fk/NpMYUWLV0g1YryvEtOBUHNN2bgGJRB/pK1d2L4ClMOQ2wvwLU3aHZ5sbVQBZClOlFE\u003d","answers":["had attended","could attend","attend","attended"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE30pbGNgZfViyYCRJP2024/N7UtBoIxvUyGFkb0qs7h1f+tiCwUm4+yl1skzXAJ72+sjsNx2JXKdw/yEbazCl6OuHea74xjucJY8plk979jn2ORq7B5QV+/Z8Z73uJGpPIrjSTysTeCmtWNGqPlYatzuGZrKzz9aqJVam2tHUyoURBCAJqS98SH31w6+7lojwszl5ShOuxLop9x/hOj+jJmk0VkLuYVlK0oEXG9IT501OhUgWgU2Ih5XxBGJ2W4OmJyHal5jlM4BFsne9yghQn0/h5RWw517zLv76B9MxS12xFnser95n7ZHSuEPqVYuz+raJVt6mXKQ7Vwp7aJfAg+rLmVjxCV13Fa6ZtxZbWFfYfDDeysPkBN7HmU808Zxd0l/z91nwiT7A1HwyT3CF/ELwgK+Eo7X+w4raj/3saUjeHrX5dz+X5V3dV+KD5SBfp6mhfITEY+8JCrMPCMxMG9n/Q91i9cMH/1K2PXkVBzkcSOuPurmADHXIL0ilzv6RSxMZst+BoVJy7d5lE+Xr0N0EIJlU3a+Nytg/lxhT/QeHfzN6UeMl8bJ6kQuzlmR5BqswFTjfscTM+lcoei+whpTo6yDgUTr+2CyjQCi8k4LP5e5uTUpRxCwcSJ4cHASNO1Glk0ecCIh9+h6fvNcSILW0tScnEJQhSFiFHIeETJBH+T9Eks5RVg43dj8g7AUWsBer64tckenDAtZSWNAu7V1hFLGpaCOMwu0XzsLhJPxtmq+R7Dkz2i4YvN+nYrtxPAETX9QG8deUdMuVlyNYGXBM1h7MVMo4xGLksxQTTjs7LtWNH6oSTHbywyOm1Z8qqnpnus1qOjzojapPvHW9zOIWI2fAKbIPGQ7OBGaip9IiH1TivPL3atTNMZ+MKxpKDxMT/1SXYttAZfF+sJMlZD1mf/DlPwG0AiJpV3gElaeDkFxmGS3Jxc/2NSGGa0tNRTEFa0UMEpG0jjaasgfgZs\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21024","langCode":"vi","question":"80EVUGk9F/JbGGUf4Q4sQt3QgYsIg19NAOyw390VM2zMp0kErmydn1UW63CSIvFE591V0ihbfUkeFPo/owA/DyA3007uP09vvq3Kvv394ZcRaKX7RloXJpg8rlqiqGQoTgf9dTDp4ognvKexwfibPfJeQtkNftiyOwaPxx9ZbeFB483wfwhg3Z0TLUKMUmuMF+UiZae0UCiX9kuZiymT4g\u003d\u003d","answers":["didn’t park","don’t park","wouldn\u0027t park","hadn’t park"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5vxgPyxYXLeuNRRAMsY0aKxB0brNBSolt8FYDN3ViOo8iZCcMslfTwRv2MpstKjWxll+ijAJe+juitIA+vUc40OfPUmJOo5Hxy0rUaMKD1lwQpQZQYp2jwQgw/UM8N56XQZsbhyOTC3LhlYrEI+JbOuLBHQ9PAvmIbMB77LEoFz7p16H5m2C8jlUTYycnQMLpbc/+ahk5Z93XHnDdA5MaVryJ3uP6DWWDDnc8rPhvtwSUSC074fbRqzi1X10Axd8JX92+mnJs4nLpxHgbctjrJZWahPhGWYpozSjfvCVqVr6hpCUm2BNNhhsIndhDoBC2DOP3QO4FJ7Om4avzLwLKe9GWJMQR1BZagvznxMt5xXXR+aFukH2ROYocz2lVjESLZ20v8A1HjkGEbPdlrmOCixuG85g2huGxYAPVJ3bx0weMOPA3RgM99grpChGI5JtvI7tRJiatnwcpnhULyJoHBmGbgLpsXwJi7FVsFUoQV3GeHLYhZDtGhesu3pmjbR8jwLBVGEYraHpqOygYIP+b87H0/Zt0LBIqTaYnDkQcaMRHPdbPQpSdjNb/4SbjG56vJr94tOujw5aJsFBgYj9Ujo99zkKay64QtcAcu/NfE/EGLH9q+Bcwz+9HjBugO0l6NtIG4ElgEE96DZ10N6EIFnhkjyxOhvNMIJEhYQSnJOzfyEQvmTdfQDhunGZ5gW3wvCAr4Sjtf7DitqP/expSN4etfl3P5flXd1X4oPlIF+nqaF8hMRj7wkKsw8IzEwb8DnX5W/8on0BX0vG428zSzmAOqXC18pnfgHmxBNKCfqa4Xt3bz/KD4UNfyZ5bxI6sdSTvdXw78GaIz3L3j+5h0oNeT2zyzt+aCgdwe009MMNeUdoSJwWaYjco1VHp9BIO9leWlz6432A4zMO8aRjJE\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21025","langCode":"vi","question":"9bGpS2iPSWYiyuJo9uBWQqE1F/aUAzg9DhaORqkZPMBrZIlt32KIk0L5Pciv7S/WUAMfGovVbnFx3b1qoY462w\u003d\u003d","answers":["rains","would rain","rained","had rained"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9H9xMlrC0Gc7r5YCEM7SyeQQ9jKEaS+d6MoPMjmu/VQIR7RoFN2LuiDM99qgkLaQl3Xy5OR7dfNXk3iVzWfFEDhXoksIUmuIUPHFeFwFlPzlPVgwZxzTYMrus7v2Ao9zWeNqgp38wAnywdt4A22YSDjnAs5KH6Xg/FIPscdIwG60l/fIofI/TSRW/wbkTOO8QQHkwXHbO2oA5x+AVyzux5BNLeZQtWtSQX8edbGJzSj/Hix3ZTs/hmNM5fs0qGIVSO4po025h/1rEdHL9XLHm/pxyo3Zxce/ohjTEHH0HQCJzBIc6j6QO0WL7j75uzpLjJTZ2+j9RB+mCVmDfxQQNpuKOFq8HkQiHUvPN0QMkBRdjyXFolVX27naMYaEH/RwLewB1H9kuajCkDO9WBYcxQEwusbnEi5dlbT0PxvsShVvbKMPTo2dhHs5YF8W+MswU8YTn59hvkunNI3kVPrydaxO9ueGz/8dpU+5QWfLOAjJCXRKE7nsKoMkT/+NEJxBswrwK/Av4hAFt0X0Uk2Ar+ARtDWqjnceDJOvsau92TvRiRi9YxHBoF9WlA8smcLM/4RUoVtbi6cCvpQP1JBewGnwVPBu7cfcg2dkLhuIgsxRsSn0FXiJSLn/4WySV4lTe0StOe/cB5QIrFKvsVv8KWQmTJ+/8dbriR+MK5g4/MHk7g0/AQRTqyfWS2j4oQIYRySDubMtFGmJNl0kNZ0/v6fZMAWdEkWMLLZTjX3MSXzJddVjwd6bsJraPJwAQ8a+bO2TJORUnR53IPEw2HCGXY\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21026","langCode":"vi","question":"0/6unznA/N+zQpSa2l0Lj3cejpCsyIdOYoXc/LE3BlcGb+8fLCTHD168noMj+DaydEUXuiid9QZnZ3KkHDPNIF/MvZSwQdLM0fAH8OQ+eK8\u003d","answers":["wouldn’t work","don’t work","hadn’t worked","didn’t work"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6RmzlQQ6OmsvwGogvRQWgPgZcSQNjKtSBtprPJeXpsgdQkpF3AqHIdsYg+RCxZF2MoiGgCyjHjCxZ321FHN0N4TYtcbjjBNbeYxMpGPu/ZdmRFdOA87PYBARmOuzL71X0GZa/4btjc9/RqIAJl9W6K2HnoE8SYBiwNyAmBZit6shTBgLbEQQJvjIKpepn7K4u8sod5idaGHzK02Q6PHd0rC+aTvxVlUqaLPY61tDTLLL02Q6inxeLEjFuUotR59PIAbx7rkbYu5jaJfiLHU1iC9BVdPfxExpkLQcJmG/sNvcs7nwmPUN626IR6jOzqVWLA2zRJ/6CEYJ1Wb2jfO0Fvvo2vAT6fpt6Aw+g5vXyo7OPqTmqoAwCbTAQVgFX35iJpWRLiTYbyfeBVWCrf9XacG4stov59xLXjXH+hslnBEMX/+Q+zK438LktVX7bSwjCtZc0L3eIFzhOeAZ1sr6e+YqQRmZ9O9nVGnfvS0rRGSl43BFGdx2tNRV0l41GDy7XUKPbSQzv2GmeMyMJms4CLvpZjRkA9EGKRRY02uQ9SehKk41ZgJBXbZ0zfD6m4icm8ldEWB6e3uKIG1dQyO30EOCmcbxefnSzKHSM2hMwz0wFnvB3cR6OriJTyzOTXZ+hgPlcUmDmQv2LMDvMGm6cvsuWq37BO8NLI9g4fgm7f3/rk7nyS4FHx7rHu41jPFrIko7LDq/Ys/dBE501iLWqPdlFBrzTS3nmGcgukqhdscYArsZ4tXl2WS/dFK6QrLs+x8M45l6nv9qqSSkoyap3265qNh7LJcfc8FTk/HzAyEPG+D1wNreeC/biW6ZnEm37VVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21027","langCode":"vi","question":"3EIxarl6TJK1ekAtDpGW70J5diDOOQ2SNV0Mie49BLb6yukfphU6IrXqvdl270F280gKvF1CdJeMuigrjN5GituLMdQPH2/0RrbtMCniAmA\u003d","answers":["would be","had been","were","are"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE24gjl71hT8X4+Owzu39k8sF5tpEMhI4G/OwKyCt9rx2pJL3g5eRk5gs4VgVEkX1+tKtR6+LkAfht4G4pdWIvz5S4dPM7U+NhhEtVkk7P5xCC6nYy9N4eqiCIrvjkOZWF2howBD0MZP0pdb819sc2Kktsq94+D8FnSNB00b1C/AB2m1zV+9g3rpQ7sqjQbmxI/a//YErOz1IU+V+DWQmuQedSnRjeU336PUd1FsO6t9f/uqKtGfKpx+fSCohG7x0x6TvXajCCd2F9Bbf1/bLxN7iUw8IhIveNkVCjA9dOZQ4jDFdMJxk9B1K0QvD/u8vlgCoCH9A4pSJ4ZLrUPp+XC5j3io1OYViuiga9Jj+xNNCvysO6FZDsNWfzfiss7nu3TPiaLfZYRbSRMLfmjACM+/9U3spm3PGjY1WG2caOrRDYcYooo7Y+O7IoS5Tt/P4dZYbjtZSvnah+Rng8CbkCHIf3cRewYi6WdrgmSzMU/QNKnN+n2HcLL+UEy63fITUg9SbPm7vz/rLOMnndCbUMRyOEB1ImRaK7cB95BHmkTHwc1oGBREjyPPWXtRhyWE3OVp63RUlQBPLI2crpHl0V0uMtNwJM+hFHtD57FGeJDLwmk/g0L/UiYP8Zvzd3c5NojR6Pi86B0aENOz43nXDy/slhF7xEBu52A5k/CBRhQWduz+Pyq8PtI5HhJOm575hwYVFAlWNSvodLIi949vlvuO6uuC1im4DUesInes+TwDTjpNAXczuQ6o2F3bIXYwP/wR3mViN4rt+Uo2CTBoZpWzY7O6/oWDTl1Z1gh16PI2dVWnaV9b60zDYJ8dqcqwxbgfSipwTzJCfqFrorEbAHVgc3Fedj1DyNh256Big3T3cBIbcJsN32BxhkONe+m1Xrj5e4eG0Ka+y/nIZbnLrVv/2Dz5lL0V3bTAni9rmATcO/sOZ7G7rH6PSSyLBwsgcbkHcBCV3eY0YmAXxiby/s6BUewJY0m6EeKglP2wBW1CXhKk41ZgJBXbZ0zfD6m4icm8ldEWB6e3uKIG1dQyO30FYPTkqbNaFC0X19kaU+6J31wXJ71YqqMPvFCnTv8O56YVzuY/BlZ0/JnxRmjkEOz9JPXQvNfj+aTwPDCulW9UgWWTyBOvUmNypYtRpo2z5mm5zcvhu1ulwjhxYwwlSglfzno25Sc/MNe6jz4OJCnt+"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21028","langCode":"vi","question":"BnFhARfmMSrVrekbPqB5oNQFMhRlcrhKBg68++CgImWgI6fzZJ9EN/NLarUlAxV/6kLLbjcAMxG8n5g+39B06g\u003d\u003d","answers":["won’t smoke","wouldn’t smoke","hadn’t smoke","don’t smoke"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6RmzlQQ6OmsvwGogvRQWgPzqMYEuUgRs5yxKNNfohCFzh/e/FujOH8CY/65W9FFdeKVKePndUMAT3+PVaJmdFf4U0aPxN9OaP84NLSljyue+uWbePTG8IoaXL+F8gPgFrRzOXt8UNv/tHEmsLpTyqf/7b3nb+sxe3AXGfwV7jJjMD380Wq8zluPQSd0npAnQaeirZOfC4FcSNgDenUrP4JkGdvU0KEN7hqGXgBgFJLhYiULWKAAaeeGCT5admxA0CO4po025h/1rEdHL9XLHm/pxyo3Zxce/ohjTEHH0HQCJzBIc6j6QO0WL7j75uzpLjJTZ2+j9RB+mCVmDfxQQNpuKOFq8HkQiHUvPN0QMkBRdjyXFolVX27naMYaEH/RwLewB1H9kuajCkDO9WBYcxQEwusbnEi5dlbT0PxvsShVvbKMPTo2dhHs5YF8W+Mswb8hSYgXLcPXG/gWBxyDauEvk6G0x9y/am4OVbIqQiq6ANLrTf/TPjmB6NVmFSAD+c/CvVkSvCWt0k0v3rDsm6XuJEmApfU9yrnccNkuienl6LrAcI1J3taXRkUHTh21atFhXkD7OHP4mdFue8OHDOUZSppIb79kaeLaQd+VyiqFGCufLdhEgiaw3kUdoAgcJJalATbfW7UmwXmFDjH/bxmC3cUs65Pt2jG5GkQalTwKl/UcvEc0APtegNu94Fn/hR3hQGmEo1ubOOq/ghqW1o0QsI/mObM3SnyYFnlebGngQuFNpQoPASH2BBLMM9MJjjx2PRY6jcU6LrhlKMD2UxK3Kej+ra39wnQFLvuVp0e0GX0NDmymGRkWryEv0k0CR9wO4/ovLVxtTPl3V9nd+SEYsu+5gRIFsvMYpLhl2D9hfL1kRsyNQKXoSZsMt1Lh80OViKL7hTgMQMrXse3ODCa3meknMIIsoW6z6yfcPfvzyYV7vqq6LnCPlrV69iPRFJLgPJ/we+8IN/U0OWyRMw9eD7ZiXj1mOvaqrOnssiu+YZJ6Ub+QrR76TjRxP6Ysvt7Bknfen2mSx4A6sqYiWXJ62v0HwT9EpJf/j0YaS5HSPZ6HQcKqj36xjdNt1DJGqgsxoCIBUBW2WmLI0/6faJaWNYfSf0FZNVrqv+IqiWH9F//V1I/zn+twSEhm3QKwP8oeyU3KwDc4knZJ8v6R2oQ4Zpn5h0ixEg3l+18vIt9ehx6eOP+2/lz+C+Kv6+QZRGwZuPQD6cAgiEi8dNLaCqA\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21029","langCode":"vi","question":"qUfWyZa2d9Bj6DhYV4DNfA5/VGn18TCcxgvx5xvITAcOe0AvdxUBxWgj8idZcX803blgWau2hnxRHzA2FtI5MA\u003d\u003d","answers":["would look","had looked","look","looked"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE3oozZJRnED21oB6Jl4SVFSeV9o/+dInzsNW4KawdxOBIR7RoFN2LuiDM99qgkLaQl3Xy5OR7dfNXk3iVzWfFEDhXoksIUmuIUPHFeFwFlPz4ejg/IWnzqN4dKovOwBmcZY1YkiYf7vh/NuUGXZgCMzQsq1UrZh+A48MOg93dPU9toP/LSsBqLpnURNQqbMn5Zo2d4KDo6QOlzNLsjW4ppS8EXpBBZl3xn6/CKQm8tzJ1ogB1QgHLEQr7BMHEGr54l9acKbaLYCnBmcpMIfoZnyPNFUNmisfk1A9wlg4i4eyIUAiJtQXcO/+HevTqHtn/Vy5D6Vy5HjEdYtRtV8QE3SMJwf9tP5ieykHyv1mFtES/0Db7WkPtesAKHKk3o3jaHux0FkMnrLHDryC1aOzYPc4Peznk1uCK7aVhYlBQv/ovRliTEEdQWWoL858TLecV/HGpcmujvL+RfnM1MKPQyXDrWR1LOmVu2cZZwnoMixd7FGiuAi8ertdjTQLehaO5j0d52p4fqwAm97/BjnNzfSLifGAUTy3YYMCxFwo784dfadNQuNHQvMawk2AfmmXnoU6fGSWmeej/V/J7BW5MK0nRMKKFROVGQVSr+EmZLne3eojCPpXB+x7vxv+NT29aQu7bg3U04bafcW343DagQ96UpkWp13LYU6622fsDTiiopLbCJCd7+X00jrVrUIc4AGZcSXsJhnPq3WwWynYrqHUGCXKKmTDrkM9UzyXflk0+W0eWfnzQQGn0/IQ5IJmbJVOVdRZ+fpRAZOvtG3wUAiVTingWOztW44KdOaqFuCd1n/DpFn91AIJbyqqjvjk+twPhQCnau0JecYgY6Y5H4K6HAz2bt7qktAEHRfxBrWoZ79MBgek1IafMKyhLVZiysBZ7wd3Eejq4iU8szk12foYD5XFJg5kL9izA7zBpunL7Llqt+wTvDSyPYOH4Ju393wRrPC3xDp0XFpuATupGGrkH7p8cPWyN1TW3cJghLvqnbJMRtSeQmzqEnGSLVkatPPOhIKG9/tqQXWXuFFbcIuAXIp+mznByDl2VwMFzAKdN0X7ln7QDa7JGX6RBkcSEs2RMrD3mXmcRL/F+meefKJkglw27flfuqiU4uhJH6n8OgPka3SNMsmAmyzJ/2PUhIcenjj/tv5c/gvir+vkGUS+eE5akohCZASor9s5lkhO"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21030","langCode":"vi","question":"qUfWyZa2d9Bj6DhYV4DNfIHnW4m1VsuoqztctLQPIEpr+kvYUADu+KBWW9KtoR8V","answers":["had stopped","stop","stopped","would stop"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9euCms+ePPFMWW7ThNjFMxEE39IftvZkEILZWXQ7OCWIR7RoFN2LuiDM99qgkLaQl3Xy5OR7dfNXk3iVzWfFEDhXoksIUmuIUPHFeFwFlPzlochpMv9Z+6BJcvvfu4E4z/OWWY7Tx5Oc2Q0+wXbNImEcpUfN8vpU3oAvo7QYT3uMSQc7Dq12qZdwXAfM1lSrjg/skN33MDDc2OfEjq+RfBoogHbZIscW7jjuvDFZvBx//HSQ1d1smT40M5B5gPiPA2tbfyDdnz+xpHEsbT0gx2ybnzwjqXmtOoLTRknKovE2hBYkcZyYMyJt3rOZFRTKhQuG40is3rBp6Qy3I09rV9J91qJE9B6vaJlPAg8Ix0E9SmDwnAgyInVg8dVOaNEP4uiFTCds1tAL4kRPNlKMmIAm3I6xXgi7KXbvDgyvNUvJ52C92fgZDFhmIl/cBHRt5t5hJxEpbDhErICEN/cniYd2A178eoKOxn+1W5bMIazS39lDN/Wr03d+E7KMIEoZOZObx2GycBrGEYgUQVcem27KovpCkyLjnezEgYoKhAojywSx9lAtGjq7YYD7RhyA8/DI1y2T+OioBq4Lm9yUoVptoeR0lYgMlAfAPElNA85Izw9Yx2d49f3IbjxstjePolANI8AGYPopoX69032KUSQVG8JFmvkUcPk7JDZIGMGPJdAMO/XEEf8F9iOI5KmyUFo2jz/nyqq3xmPiIuX0B8I2EjWT0JIgUlaTdaW6wcbymCS5HxcxchUZXasYnNGxjGFv7D6nzs3jMsoVY3jF8bqFVKQfiMHQidzcIfNT7wihrw9EdnKUHeqK/FcROXMkpUOUdfxOg9RrtqfSn5PmP/jGmbSOfxQpNcCNjTnVRjG0eD0r4CeHFgHkNMti29ITuQfunxw9bI3VNbdwmCEu+qdskxG1J5CbOoScZItWRq0TklnGQG7lUD3OGTBh+j0OVODncy8UH7x8RrgxRtecZ/2Dz5lL0V3bTAni9rmATcO/sOZ7G7rH6PSSyLBwsgcbusvt2+wnFiwuVIKn5X8C0bugGs7M8zcun06aE1nd41BlgTLWfDmOsKuNK/NgjKN6EzjMLVBeS4qZv5AABhj7VOiYsYE+kkfZ/3S5FenrZWTgQ1uaVJZkku19ti+UtKCarG4AJUz+TUwZiL9BS9qy52T7jOEVnji2L4NjOG/uyvy"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21031","langCode":"vi","question":"80EVUGk9F/JbGGUf4Q4sQmo2AY4aQyM/R5bcqTOSn3WUBU6Y5tc7OZfVVLXcZTxW","answers":["argue","argued","had argued","wouldn\u0027t argue"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5vxgPyxYXLeuNRRAMsY0aJErNheGEke0dNWR+uVvwbdnMdqQu7gEhm6SrxI8gjyl2cMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuJ5xrkD+YlLkV1dDG+62aiZWH1OeFdicWfEBEIUo+A68xA18uTvft9sutR65mCMP4PWF7uxtnhyLbzUySz9kVsQLo5WNyMK7hnA4cDBZW5/5ZnGaXK65zA9VnwcCqckGurve5VheM2VQXATX98vIGZ4+F5+GxgHr2eDuV74qPGe0NVBN5N8OyghEaDiuUVRVhtNaUFktGA/zXQfi7aJFZGzSqEZsGHgcB+hwn53AMp1MA2Sziq6BC70gTA8QJtjc4P30GU8MjaV/yHcS/jo9L74QlsMSI7QQVl2LnDn1skj2TyXQDDv1xBH/BfYjiOSpskjNZxOXYl3M0cJ7/Fgn+/yVK0jTY0DgK/WIsWGwFPb2m8E98rrhKc5wUsIa/AIt7LyciA847a2y7YrPvhWy/YFR3X5MtOOxU2xmM8x9x5u2d8CwyGIVNCVhYHCPziOe9/kPSXJEa0QsFUdVwJWwMEmcI7Zp0T+iYNXSDPueCh2l3Rn+wCKEq4Qw59V/Lg1Z3x00YrnN2++HFbPk6wMjqi27p6EE4jDKoopDJvLodkLwvdg7oSM6LyvmBZtJMEFq+6XJcSFsUUGmVTkOY6oVgcdZn4hHELCOvW6iXvqsiK85fO80KWKDQ8ow4AvJGhKnaYniM/vtG+t0s/Sndu1MlNDkcBz6cCaisPHutaUQiWI9gkAXaHoIfzOddOEYmnvxnV/osC/9lPkW4qv6y42CHMuhExSY79qv3jNCYBfdMQywTwdJUijONDq6h8c3qPQFV7o99zkKay64QtcAcu/NfE/EGLH9q+Bcwz+9HjBugO0l6NtIG4ElgEE96DZ10N6EIFnhkjyxOhvNMIJEhYQSnJOzfyEQvmTdfQDhunGZ5gW3wvCAr4Sjtf7DitqP/expSN4etfl3P5flXd1X4oPlIF+nqaF8hMRj7wkKsw8IzEwb8DnX5W/8on0BX0vG428zSzmAOqXC18pnfgHmxBNKCfqa4Xt3bz/KD4UNfyZ5bxI6sdSTvdXw78GaIz3L3j+5h3tk+q+b0+Ab4bbJIlGzqSruuajYeyyXH3PBU5Px8wMhDxvg9cDa3ngv24lumZxJt9UP3jDOBOeSWYwxXdbINBU"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21032","langCode":"vi","question":"af/5fDZKnT0xSHgcfpA4SvaMnCmW4K1kfhHaXGJL6mnSH3YhsWlPdHxXBK9mPTL6","answers":["find","will find","could find","had found"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEyfwsS/S6hZRit563hewoB4Sf7X6l6IcZ4K4hdNQmgI8IR7RoFN2LuiDM99qgkLaQl3Xy5OR7dfNXk3iVzWfFEBgG6oBrtm04dCRvNuRQol2h8RgGFWf/LI375E5ZGPIq6ddm9ccKwjSevGHfhM6zkfyQ0UAcBxbH1NDuoDcijGClFOxQK0iMaN4JXC75AhUSq8w2ZpwpW9ljfDUzRMpuktwsxQ7CDDfMF0x3eK00k9+dgQc1sW1Hl6+3mNN0WP4esMwXDJUtuwqIM66h1CedZC6Q19a9AYU6/fpNLzsvsMDeDdhHo55gSp/yhUW18kr9dhgjIxt1TPtydrf8aLF/enRS00HkpSgnlzTJULmX++qkmF3ablVFEssBnNGXklH7/fUY3kefmDTgT3ORPI15qXBrK3+yqOoy1v40Hzq8Sru87B2hBRIUVa2HL/S6DzzW/5iFznIyt1wWq7yXg1SCpHewZJ33p9pkseAOrKmIllyetr9B8E/RKSX/49GGkuR0gGBXpGnLZK7MOwAUhwTJxgfxyaExIcIXdaSG0qnQTMcOaHclLHygjKgdK9UggpfX8zNeIpUN3MPnJkwA6mSyRqVdq4BuwIMsNt5h9Gr5mUe82Jwq/vajHKVdpFiah6XPdKTXDO+dL3/n5PcFyiR9nziYL8sxgeAQnr/8ESCDnTtYNIRxP7ebek3FU+ePWR60G5zcvhu1ulwjhxYwwlSglfzno25Sc/MNe6jz4OJCnt+"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21033","langCode":"vi","question":"IA79Clf5O6uCD3io5HBfrJa4q0T0IGigUY25HywbL3RJm3LJk028j0krKSidLOUxcMGbZx35ZhB+DdDXO9E6GFMbh8F1XlmpjQCwwKfluv4\u003d","answers":["had stopped","stop","would stop","will stop"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9euCms+ePPFMWW7ThNjFMxEE39IftvZkEILZWXQ7OCWIR7RoFN2LuiDM99qgkLaQl3Xy5OR7dfNXk3iVzWfFEDRO3McCSFtSO6vx8UhaqswaAeRUHZlx1S8FDUSU42+cFSN3jiJoQur/eV2QskAZKuBk/Ala3tsx0x/xVaCsmdEA9GYF58w077Xv9AH+51gXjbrTFz4Vrp4me3qp7kjqvY4P7JDd9zAw3NjnxI6vkXwaKIB22SLHFu447rwxWbwcf/x0kNXdbJk+NDOQeYD4jwNrW38g3Z8/saRxLG09IMdsm588I6l5rTqC00ZJyqLxNoQWJHGcmDMibd6zmRUUyoULhuNIrN6waekMtyNPa1fSfdaiRPQer2iZTwIPCMdBPUpg8JwIMiJ1YPHVTmjRD+LohUwnbNbQC+JETzZSjJiAJtyOsV4Iuyl27w4MrzVLyedgvdn4GQxYZiJf3AR0bebeYScRKWw4RKyAhDf3J4mHdgNe/HqCjsZ/tVuWzCGs0t/ZQzf1q9N3fhOyjCBKGTmTm8dhsnAaxhGIFEFXHptuyqL6QpMi453sxIGKCoQKI8sEsfZQLRo6u2GA+0YcgPPwyNctk/joqAauC5vclKFabaHkdJWIDJQHwDxJTQPOSM8PWMdnePX9yG48bLY3j6JQDSPABmD6KaF+vdN9ilEkFRvCRZr5FHD5OyQ2SBjBjyXQDDv1xBH/BfYjiOSpslBaNo8/58qqt8Zj4iLl9AfCNhI1k9CSIFJWk3WlusHG8pgkuR8XMXIVGV2rGJzRsYxhb+w+p87N4zLKFWN4xfG6hVSkH4jB0Inc3CHzU+8Ioa8PRHZylB3qivxXETlzJKVDlHX8ToPUa7an0p+T5j/4xpm0jn8UKTXAjY051UYxtHg9K+AnhxYB5DTLYtvSE7kH7p8cPWyN1TW3cJghLvqnbJMRtSeQmzqEnGSLVkatE5JZxkBu5VA9zhkwYfo9DlTg53MvFB+8fEa4MUbXnGf9g8+ZS9Fd20wJ4va5gE3Dv7Dmexu6x+j0ksiwcLIHG7rL7dvsJxYsLlSCp+V/AtG7oBrOzPM3Lp9OmhNZ3eNQZYEy1nw5jrCrjSvzYIyjehM4zC1QXkuKmb+QAAYY+1TomLGBPpJH2f90uRXp62Vk4ENbmlSWZJLtfbYvlLSgmqxuACVM/k1MGYi/QUvasudd2xwu08jI/aFNKpA53cp/w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21034","langCode":"vi","question":"qUfWyZa2d9Bj6DhYV4DNfEaqDn/tWDpY4dNIXs7nzj009MWsngoLHhbGKfa5HyekS5lZ5uH1958XkSAS3ZUOBA\u003d\u003d","answers":["would use","wouldn’t use","had used","use"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6RmzlQQ6OmsvwGogvRQWgPmc40LZ0RFAaGQoTl0wZpunMdqQu7gEhm6SrxI8gjyl2cMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuJ5xrkD+YlLkV1dDG+62aiZmxqr72DYOiqrwtC4ArkFZNSd7CSlMcH6GIENrSHMPkM9548qtc5eO24sBnTuqiHErwa9R6/PF1DZfVMpeEHullyfyJI23UVnjBAFV8m9Zu68zV3HccSVR7HMIDeyfZ1XzOXlKE67Euin3H+E6P6MmaTRWQu5hWUrSgRcb0hPnTU6FSBaBTYiHlfEEYnZbg6YnIdqXmOUzgEWyd73KCFCfT+HlFbDnXvMu/voH0zFLXbEWex6v3mftkdK4Q+pVi7P6tolW3qZcpDtXCntol8CD6suZWPEJXXcVrpm3FltYV8p/SwoQ1sWk1HwKR3mg575myY33bHu5ltnVCqJAohlh2MxuTcdFUQ2jZYKPmmIUDO8X8IQNBr6yXKxUqjz0skiz+rAys47agq8I7C2GBoxwhs9nXO1WEdOxas+JRDstfftkIikdQPZGrXjuAyGfLpUGY0hwYTVvpqrClP/LHHls2HivNOcTLs3e0RU3/mB0lM9jl/SeGmywhyLt57jya+5vSnuiFOIlu002cqtR8hW/8RNs3Jws+3ZCIwugE4pm/Kvggf9LhO+puqUaVGAyL3kZ1VtF+xI313D33YJU47+Pc1pkbVt16zTYZabmkHflpavlpFM8NHgzkG2A2nQ9jiQXJpBOig5KVpTWPSueKS/u0y17M534EaysP7F4liiqXcKaBtDboZNN/s+2VR55IlUr5kbQteJlO2cTBfJeLehax0w+UtEC83wVxBnW/giacboyHR/d72CJ53gfFA+22yJj7RGd8WTXLY2WMOuNzpPP0ddfv01oKoUZ8iFgEDIl0YD3mey0wo0SeXS4Nb6vauxtH25zjALV/OnuxJelk5o3eORKyH28Cp0kBBw1T+02ODJhXu+qroucI+WtXr2I9EUkuA8n/B77wg39TQ5bJEzD4SaSEYE3iZ8MXo9yYM8mOC5pdcBQkbJUVtFGgdHJHblLA6aR8ZMbPx5fAUFPKfprQ2O1Wz4iP3sm9DJy1z4RLzjPPWc9uXY+hFn5dYdCEJbGQV9fI8phJ9i2zK81/WVEK5/qg5HWfDsyhlRJOp9gvanYhHuYh/pYi6RAQd5xdLV"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21035","langCode":"vi","question":"vx/FHwanMAN4R5AQGWrmgu/NPi5u1GKzLgr3WtM5Zrk4iHaXO6u6DYt19+UcUpulj75OskRmQpw7JDLW/0QtJA\u003d\u003d","answers":["went","goes","will go","would go"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEyOh68p0iOdLGZJv3tEcpgRrvmrxhFefWQ4R+kv9oB9UpJL3g5eRk5gs4VgVEkX1+tKtR6+LkAfht4G4pdWIvz75tTGNHMNHdK3R7qdzSOdk6dbRsh2MIiuqbaRtqYg+iX0S6yqLpbZyvYockEIkaP5KAJE/n9Cxo6im1SA1p0mbgcPO+IylZLVpOnwLpEFjgQKcA4xjULdxM9KMbA8D4pKZxmlyuucwPVZ8HAqnJBrq73uVYXjNlUFwE1/fLyBmePhefhsYB69ng7le+KjxntDVQTeTfDsoIRGg4rlFUVYbTWlBZLRgP810H4u2iRWRs0qhGbBh4HAfocJ+dwDKdTANks4qugQu9IEwPECbY3OD99BlPDI2lf8h3Ev46PS++EJbDEiO0EFZdi5w59bJI9k8l0Aw79cQR/wX2I4jkqbJIzWcTl2JdzNHCe/xYJ/v8lStI02NA4Cv1iLFhsBT29pvBPfK64SnOcFLCGvwCLey8nIgPOO2tsu2Kz74Vsv2BUd1+TLTjsVNsZjPMfcebtnfAsMhiFTQlYWBwj84jnvf5D0lyRGtELBVHVcCVsDBJnCO2adE/omDV0gz7ngodpd0Z/sAihKuEMOfVfy4NWd8dNGK5zdvvhxWz5OsDI6otu6ehBOIwyqKKQyby6HZC8L3YO6EjOi8r5gWbSTBBavulyXEhbFFBplU5DmOqFYHHWZ+IRxCwjr1uol76rIivOXzvNClig0PKMOALyRoSp2mJ4jP77RvrdLP0p3btTJTQ5HAc+nAmorDx7rWlEIliPYJAF2h6CH8znXThGJp78Z1f6LAv/ZT5FuKr+suNghzLoRMUmO/ar94zQmAX3TEMsE8HSVIozjQ6uofHN6j0BVe6Pfc5CmsuuELXAHLvzXxPxBix/avgXMM/vR4wboDtJejbSBuBJYBBPeg2ddDehCBZ4ZI8sTobzTCCRIWEEpyTs38hEL5k3X0A4bpxmeYFt8LwgK+Eo7X+w4raj/3saUjeHrX5dz+X5V3dV+KD5SBfp6mhfITEY+8JCrMPCMxMG/A51+Vv/KJ9AV9LxuNvM0s5gDqlwtfKZ34B5sQTSgn6muF7d28/yg+FDX8meW8SOrHUk73V8O/BmiM9y94/uYdfG8I7uVVzuuuWWWPPapR0tbS1JycQlCFIWIUch4RMkEtr65rojuasLoKF/N0o2Wx"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21036","langCode":"vi","question":"v+0gKAzvqFPgkg5jJX6MJ1d0Ao84J6s7nFlxkdB55BmEWTN0jebn/qbTdYR9YnRo","answers":["to speak","will speak","speak","spoke"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4pNhuyxVwdRhckjjtbTd8O/y9XEZ24vn7wSkmnQBUE93u4e8nySwlg50WYVI4bDjoGfnIr9WEKPwJU/l9JwvWQEB5MFx2ztqAOcfgFcs7selhuO1lK+dqH5GeDwJuQIcqCoaHkEdtxHeenSm3hqULruwe4GB9Ppr/2Fy368Ty7fxSnt0G9vJSkfPTIJ5RX8d2ljvfk4/iD/CgVaH4HWUd2HCD6IZrjuUVe3hq4E2/1bmYL6vC1B3CIFg2M4ttIquxCOrtV7gZmZPJvF0IaKtil9H6MOXhbrlf5Ef+vNz2DR7kNV1DqIWsD97iqLSSGpgsYkN0dWdyzhiQcaeTir8NyI7N3iGpA1UeqqyckkNZ+Nw9GEcP1PYFRC63nwtsBPryL5QJDX3s2mF4MHPmwu4iWdi51jb5IWUlen/qO80632lCYwS1i3+zzjEUlNDkhxfcPH9FwMsxXx6YqbwsYShtWHKcqSbW+vGX2Oje4jTph7opQV2TsvHGoMytlj/gogF5bcxxld1DOXaIz9asumwgN/Z40oMrB04kbmu10SXm0l8uNnbLrimayZ95K1NG4XWV3Xy5OR7dfNXk3iVzWfFECjHyt8eG23eL0unw6wMHMDHXtunTBeNj+1+1At1HPdqesFgLo8pNQMczkOv1kMXwdDlu7gwc0Z1TE3q+xhlB+f"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21037","langCode":"vi","question":"jKvAFjjePcZ7TlhzuFRWXdSMI/ZNRhdrY3dLbS7qpAq8fFzMYi2kxYAe07EervXaW0i6JFqSA5QZNNZ9TZ0zIw\u003d\u003d","answers":["visited","visit","to visit","will visit"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE0RRateLFMWZvoNasKhp+rS/y9XEZ24vn7wSkmnQBUE93u4e8nySwlg50WYVI4bDjoGfnIr9WEKPwJU/l9JwvWQEB5MFx2ztqAOcfgFcs7selhuO1lK+dqH5GeDwJuQIcqCoaHkEdtxHeenSm3hqULruwe4GB9Ppr/2Fy368Ty7fxSnt0G9vJSkfPTIJ5RX8d2ljvfk4/iD/CgVaH4HWUd2HCD6IZrjuUVe3hq4E2/1bmYL6vC1B3CIFg2M4ttIquxCOrtV7gZmZPJvF0IaKtil9H6MOXhbrlf5Ef+vNz2DR7kNV1DqIWsD97iqLSSGpgsYkN0dWdyzhiQcaeTir8NyI7N3iGpA1UeqqyckkNZ+Nw9GEcP1PYFRC63nwtsBPryL5QJDX3s2mF4MHPmwu4iWdi51jb5IWUlen/qO80632lCYwS1i3+zzjEUlNDkhxfcPH9FwMsxXx6YqbwsYShtWHKcqSbW+vGX2Oje4jTph7opQV2TsvHGoMytlj/gogF5bcxxld1DOXaIz9asumwgN/Z40oMrB04kbmu10SXm0l8uNnbLrimayZ95K1NG4XWV3Xy5OR7dfNXk3iVzWfFEA3OqWQqbL/FLaN45pQuJgY3PVxg2bPQ8Gl+AXqOjzSyrJgnsa1UdoERxOCv9tIPqgRZMMAse404bxcn2AKIhBy7bY6IAtICjijPsTbeoUUZurEWp7SUbnzERdXnJNFd4o\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21038","langCode":"vi","question":"IzZLVf3vz22vBeGdKDqmpmj0hNC1JvruJ5bWxQ4PTXLpno2tHyoKVtdqm8mNr59iycTRw+8m/nUtEi990y3jrzK4mNrarGPE1duPaH4ZWy4\u003d","answers":["knew","to know","would know","know"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7my7TdwPeCbTBMwG5lXxAFN8pEzIbFCRINhf2mRvbYkX/OU4Nefnuo9QbqlePEPPj7lAiyCTZYDnnOTE6dU3sa3Ia0qwbg/0wWA4mCltWKPT94vC58PGHjLUjVuUjT8HLwxhA5dnYVABIcsMeYQV95ZvGmsLYRW8NgoRH6ln85zsDOcPcqC2zh9wlo5djIMR9j1wG6Mzf9rhZAbnCEHX4Y7slT6VzlRwVfTAx9vlMmXQYcRc7GwOPafwejiaKsuscOA/ZCiNEEpJY1q2FiTkC49lEZtg0ID+TKG5sGv3a30tAJkumVL2V6GEsyeGeiA1Dr+YQS8RL1mEr2YoQy9sURV0Cqm+o6B7sMYAYwf8EOkoRT9qnUrQ/w07mkyqgcjDjVtE435P2CdxQoMPwr1n8DQijLrCAssod+WgydR0uA9W1nFkZ7bhcKPzPdcj3iUmy4v7Js/by9hdfwEhJybIrqSzH0wBpLuYmjTINjc3NH8i0anjlK4NDot2m4ttGfI8wMYVjT7hElhTUV/utEO6FF1cZFgShJv6GVMYyY+iiU8shn/2qOAGLgrvFo+3Eq8KheQjivY/pEN4OWgNJrBmAklJvQgOAGoksJO+MV7umzXwla8AOZcjKwxI1Gl3xR5siou6jijdn36lXeGuGRZvV/1bKrys2FsNT7v9voZcjDLjniwCSUO1siWABWV8dUrZINtt/wMhxMQVgR5r3CkRBGNaV7JltrCPoV+5qRylWlUcHYZAjFWnp8CBYokbSSknsjOdtUjsMbqx1QFPgFNMVo\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21039","langCode":"vi","question":"w3/c5GerkPx6zuo0OZtUluND6g343KOTCjPtDbrcMONSu09i85ErYgxDbwzrCRFM","answers":["had","to have","have","could have"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEyf57kVhf9ruhGVG2m3L2I5N8pEzIbFCRINhf2mRvbYkX/OU4Nefnuo9QbqlePEPPouSoHOgyxrSt9GA7a/wOhsFblFv1wgc9o8kUsRp6dbnBjKOZKaJJ7Nrc1SUWfcROWZTGQ2u7Pg93MQ68Oj3ibE/I+BLoOgI2m8aR86uxIz1dW6VmPs2584WUnUbBz4CZfhf5q++1Meh0b9vuASrXLOHYoCj3/9gZgGiu8CORgQMOv9hyNb6JTkHW+s63sfq/TM0mYL0nFjIPzt3otTdn+F5OsOTImsIaarJiwKmbaKgnC791VF8CFT8b/R99Ymbsd13iMTg2judkqWZUtRReFrcSJ+ugDG2eyhEVMkPJc4IySpCSpcwCz6EJpaVnMKT2LbdHjpcfL3rqIGawv5MYyOQES/KmOJieb3Off0okl43TOMP95qRZstvT9vl/rPMxJ0DQ5vITVI25z0sOPPNGFU35HrUEaFdIvr4FYYOAdozutodhsbU2Ydxs8BZ0s7IA41p+vcEtwJstxPIs2HoYM2fjmZ/r3XSGWU5pmYMGFqXUOQUf8r7OUlewfxrN2jOrceck84pN7OED5FVlqxAEmq9qSeEkTwrBpvKMMhLeL0fQGY1kHFbdnvdqhO35xa0jC/71jkTelxoopqCz4p+Ot3/HauRAQiOCtpH0JRYagyz"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21040","langCode":"vi","question":"qUfWyZa2d9Bj6DhYV4DNfLHyiZ91nj6IWAGnLrUptW5IT1Jc21wWtqo4ytTnLhrm","answers":["success","successful","successfully","succeed"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE07GN1py81qjYJ9kh6DA3Ld/sM1C12ui009lzqenLiWiU30QMxxXH6CEk87ZUqiYlA7d+4Djzi1vT8Qf4CT8cLgztER86+iRRi69ulaPKgQFan2Ct/dKwgWOQIkrA8QKTpyjMOLcUV/mgnTT21bh7GnRwDbvruz2ifa3P8KIi0Y5ULLy6vS33+mgY7M6ShsUQRUhC2rZXrrTeiX9f6Ofnc/p6n8QQABvTSSq/0sNKaa+OIpmsMU5WZFkaHcYr48/ZVmJiC/783LDP2LzXDZ9qqtBXuPTzSTpkPHe1ntR1qlBS3jM2XVoN+BF13mDfAiVL7VaNp3c5EweUVQwtA9emAJhQYavP0kedaojS9OCqwG6Ovg9GUYpdXLmyYiG3h6Kgtjte0RGt+423DciWnFVpYBB3nMbhXeZn6a8EQUqtz1OJ52C92fgZDFhmIl/cBHRt9GaDAY39fb0P3u6sxbiz2kwRcCNY2701j0E9vQWsm+DF//V1I/zn+twSEhm3QKwP7bvYe3HewF+Hn1OZTF9C40J2gj3aw14QKu3PtV3dZAe2rjEagcx2fbWDWZvDQVrf0UnxSwTUO8M0TmXTLp6OGTug9VfQbDSlReG62l2lM5902bkDLuzkhYBy1+0Rgyp7QAOBR8ENb8GjIljrS19vMN16Na9axB08V9PqlQfx/uNHSdN6yZW+cRr7jK+jeERfw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21041","langCode":"vi","question":"xor8TMhcHlaoRkTFRfRYkl4A9LRJhPYnlJZRd6kligJUKp74bk0eKthdVkpSc8xiIZnLCw87RB9NJomKEaqLuQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["luckily","to luck","lucky","luck"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7kbWH5PRFmEpAn9Z39YgDIljuM0AA1i2DWhalG+FjGcWxIxxt8R9pkh1G/bkTjh+fFdk5UvoGRepte13BBYHBXihNlJF724WXhsE/wAhdXH/mW3HDFVPh3QL4mC/3rXAGPfIf3Mma4DN7CX7mTCuc+UjW9HltoVo1Bw7Fen8hLZ7kXIQgGN7sgwAUWYStN3unjViDsj5KsCz/7uTaW+5UWOMniVKd3m0bXI+0VNx0hfz1qlblyGOIBZmXuJe5a4ZXYP6zLN7poUMiy/RRXLP954cgpts2K0jAbj9woYxXBOGDjoLnu1nFXms/44QCDLIc/x3RmM2qJZD9WPUOv9y4D6wNkAnJBx1GjNfsvmMcijgBvHuuRti7mNol+IsdTWIBrNUi8JLDbmZR5CXInjpVUfEshLcMjqIsrzfIzCtHsTgGymRm+54tcDvctsrWKB+MFOHN+187MMlZG6qJlxZa6x7p8Dzrb1MxezEOCbWRYGXURdh2T3qCnApjN6sE3fvRCoVI4MWGgl+NwFR9/tvQEZZfoowCXvo7orSAPr1HONNjVY3ttKhQqJl4iIUNISHUOvM3kZ38oe2VbwxzhUC9uWIHrmlVEAei+1nnmT7f1KuxSvq6GotoZmj8NgIQ9fzbIeYW20GsFgTzj9LzZeLuK1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21042","langCode":"vi","question":"WxMXwKwHMfSMhbaP7CVOytx2YlDXKlKtW5SFQillApI\u003d","answers":["living a long and happy life","a long and happy life","lived a long and happy life","had lived a long and happy life"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeExj/cBzSh3VJ4EbEEj6Btk7z3wEbaEQllzT4/+LyCL7Tsf7CiElmutiBu84JKST49kZiPJqUDoHsO1YrCyaLiXmRatT+Fx8g/oVT2K1XJOKDk0s0VI5HlKD0HbxqRmaDgjOS4MWyA5yVrtz7cg83+vtxVM+J9ZEEg7DUge+YPWuvzBF5JiSUaEVFQGY1/+lsBgDrDAieTuwNvLba+OYwA06CdQQFNHgj2JuUKyXezfZ5iVAl8SQmRCNl0bFIB9ypCEvCU3jicb4a9A1ta/Kw5qIVOIiCfslehQonW1eQQ82QuI5+yNXU/uY9P/Rp+Qf4eC6OmjogEYbez0VWJMhBIZyYoi8F1EC3nWIg3FGkx1SdqukwpKjpMLuopphDwCJS4DBC0u1RF0Y7X6636nIvGf3XBcnvViqow+8UKdO/w7npddTPsmRZFuQ7hDWfRzDpf/b9bj3JaytGpBHqiwrjM4PyWEnOGEmWM1vSk9zo2SeEC9WYFREaUBoBTYs3V2UGrKPeP5t48Xfcz5t1npyi6pNsboxZewjlqX/RSTwLVsz12DY6byUbF2K5py7PJJIXb1sSOc8rSqDcnRRDyqrweQ9yvYcFqYqSqpVyXYbG8r1DGRmAEgoY6sYMaUQVxPX6cnTRqfPS/Sh0r8gpJKNWAAbv1lnWgyahcuCARZu526CD"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21043","langCode":"vi","question":"qUfWyZa2d9Bj6DhYV4DNfKObfoJoL0i9Z1C7jVCQGsc\u003d","answers":["had had a safe and pleasant journey","had a safe and pleasant journey","a safe and pleasant journey","having a safe and pleasant journey"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEz8TB4BjZPZN+Q0X0J8d1uFomXjEqFrjNjLi6vljeb6Dk89hImDTi0RWibtfnuYIIy6J3kmGjXsnr+b/jbhOAuuOMniVKd3m0bXI+0VNx0hfFMMfO55fPtPhjKMCZFLbBpyMA1lF67KmrKV4/LaADB5XffOA4dLhfatpQzCK1BgO5ZWbedu4pimJQBYISfCs5p5zKNSeexIG2AuzUYjpTHOgaAmi2UMrnEdHtX9JrJO1TyUR66TmBY9Mlz9svK0n5o0z17bH3fG9g6TcMg48dBzOQAjtXZiTjSN71U/fpOHO1vySK9AR3e4GOoK9NA5EVMZBzjwIQQiRAF0RMGkoGEgkuhtj9rL5VxfPln+Fx4wBLiPHZTpR3lBq74065hg6tC+TobTH3L9qbg5VsipCKroeWg4hE9tIyqQoKnUpmRYSXpSfHeA/LaZKVqJSCXBRTkk9dC81+P5pPA8MK6Vb1SAjfRMXHdl6KzM2Uws0eNYb5jMVTeHVCLDUuKgEuuYY5Lrmo2Hsslx9zwVOT8fMDIQ8b4PXA2t54L9uJbpmcSbfOuTrPcCApa8PiRzyFp2cOr2rUdBnGRPTd1qJquzcU21Z/qghATszM9p6knS8Z7E4CEwEuafYOAPj9ywpuCtumfEy2kiWwVHt/iDP/5p7INkRhZ2ZqRsZJ04EHMUKpRu9tVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21044","langCode":"vi","question":"9ctQghowDMlS7UkTOp4+j7hRdSyygouIn2NhbhENtIbJRPF493y9t7le1ryf3eJc","answers":["punish","to punish","will punish","punished"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEyRXLvJQKt4e55mbqRMw0eN5gNIhMsmzcP9eZ+jaJbMeB/YrSrrmUeROBX3lQNIT6ldRiyDdPH9+0IGR76FzQ4Pww85DjMO0yPOhq5KimmwKwQFPT/2l/RdLqf7OK/JlYRdruepmt2kw2Xya3r770+rJ1wlrRRNDNQsrLBoFkolz8ju1EmJq2fBymeFQvImgcGIHGH0CwCe3GczfitrSa5qjAHxZ+hwD7RdusQgefFHSB6nI7W71tsMXwkouMwW8/AD0ZJckVLR7Ux5i41LUnNQLMaAiAVAVtlpiyNP+n2iWljWH0n9BWTVa6r/iKolh/ZtXeJSxnpfOfMMmZI8k1cS86RxzCnhwnxbYX5QxGC8CJddVjwd6bsJraPJwAQ8a+bc5ijXpIEoiVGBIpwd1GJRvdgUd6daGfU8Cry6ic99MJ43aC5j1Y8Jqpw+vCe/E6736FfL86HDVYLp6BxxHLO8rWhsoVLkbnAX7gGUUa59FfOxA96HAT8pLGAGen2iQx8cS74RC7a7SpYGV5s2y8ZhS7kQ2o37Jwy9EY1dqQWkd"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21045","langCode":"vi","question":"udjY6gBTnwL/CSFhEE62wkY8wy3Dg7o5HF3TZES0ER/Mpj8E6CFhRoddX3i0Ws0S","answers":["have joined","join","to join","joining"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeExznV0i/484K/1hMtf3aQDeNaw5ssY67wdvCOWT6xkpNP6H3rkUaL6+0DZgxHDx9Ql+eOoCJYfnOTZxHy+orLjb+QjDDGFRPnFMU1PWcFUQUZ0rlNnVMe1Kv1DA8SkVQJAKhh3GB3aVsKZ6aQqVgrq1di476tDnleQfeOZoyxTKcN2mh0To6fPQ/x26KDP99s8+PN9dgFhDXBLpNssgBsBkoaDgiWN9anLtGFJ113a1ZTLZ4VhZACl67h6L0uJRaOognEXidgvbZBf4ASYumL+nXBcnvViqow+8UKdO/w7nphXO5j8GVnT8mfFGaOQQ7P+FeEYLSP1WJZo6OIC1/V6zlecB+x2qSbydytB3myjb+fQLlRVAmojxUCgsy0s8vwF5hYgG9d4MJB/kYuo7HH+TjnAOvho+VpnAMSz6/IXT8nz9HyvoH0z6jc5oJ+HeUJKAyZBxSkC9VetcDRTbgpvpM4LxiMLyDeYplLYTlwDhGVdqpkOvESXq8tAoX0Je7dbmaxmcMSy1vcNzjDvDfBWkjNpF1M8NR1NFp6xKryd0u"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21046","langCode":"vi","question":"nPuU/pU5xttGTUi4TofEm2WXuC8exK5VjqlhMpTGdWm3h+FQGZxyeIsSFR0Telwl6rGrxTes4DvOMnK3Vae3iy0x6DQVbDR9pWAxJuDz56E\u003d","answers":["is","being","be","were"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8G1+oTMiX1dSJkDQnjfpPVeqc/oBgdi/83vZLnrt8hQg2XqG92FRNbGqUW4VUnHx5cE+EJrU2IAVEAUfjGfooFWUm/Ma7ig7+ZAXGcfvpQoWJ2vOLONXMqfEUo9ewOWooy1n4JyzVqH65QHg3ISrgUDKS4MuNEGwxBuUifhkFyu9kkSpVBYjd2QznNxe/6576Ju0itNuqrNBGupHc3zYyCDp0qpiG/37s88Sxn1cpFNM5LgxbIDnJWu3PtyDzf6+999ymvGOtbBMpCkSgYS62y7J/X4EJHNHlA584CLZTpf+jJDIPdRnjoU602VpBvCMqMNo3/iQPGz/zafu0vre/oGvPaT0dLIJZbdYKwQgHh4mHv6/6wPpdn0+VXvC1qu8IOPa6OV730pxeZy866wXxlP3PJYarLCmol+E9Tv2QT0cVR86UdcOViGVRIFhN7N4dQ6B0K1Fyd51dGGiEyc6FxFJ8UsE1DvDNE5l0y6ejhk7oPVX0Gw0pUXhutpdpTOfQUk3CRJ9g+rDlJPQPO67ob3VacQEf2n4sdYJkwSmVTlUT8J+Cm4WWSzTBwUaOkOsJJRoDf4h/eiIj0W8bRzni4K1T8ArNP0olqO6/PHQNCE9Mz8fC900O76ao1YAic17w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21047","langCode":"vi","question":"MxoKhpgKHUqAaAi/GXlhe8r56BGId+N7/yHE8V8w9BhAhwKh5ds2tbnd63sJGLk1QKZdHRCmB+CdhEKUawSFVQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["has listened","listening","had listened","listens"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE3dELi7rUOJo7OnqwW6kw74vICass3V45TdlgCwPZuNnaqnGp+7qwnctNZEUIZDDkcWYt/0wh6bZjCaTOgmD3q9RjrH+6HaOXswzvD9EMn3kmNCPCcz3X7mU4KZA4v4596Sd051rn5tGL+vwUsfyYtUH5v5h83ZsuUV7bSaZd0TfvaHq/XNfos4owfwgN33NhEF1TYVyYhOlQM3aCR41zefPr8//RehuwQguxf/vnbSuWeMp0CbZVyf/pofjaPnXWWzAVibOaxYgRqYw9aF6D/xqfYK390rCBY5AiSsDxApO91ormxJQb8/RWRvSKBnDzVT9JrSVcH6AjB3QHZEcMoNqaM1i9s6q1OL+yq6nng+REcyvFuN0rN3mJF2y16zA17x+qw2VyYq0/KVXR2bly0Co/VjWWcwPg1Pihl5okziusYMgnoSxKN4ZjclfmZf/dOZytMI9q3fGL0JFqJGNiAANrW38g3Z8/saRxLG09IMdIH46L7LYsQBQiqFmGiwh6nH/TzX3z7MGTmjgIaH5jdLe/b1/zVGMfjokDrTwIcxJtnn86zLz6vCum21P9JMqalDkFH/K+zlJXsH8azdozq3HnJPOKTezhA+RVZasQBJqLBTito7QXE2edH7nmc2DXaWDsqJZtcQstLjoZjRGbQjFAktoO/6m/SxpNANZQMZ0gGeUdsA4pmBtrFSqD+mfT5j880LK4BiacbZ1174biZy1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21048","langCode":"vi","question":"AzGcr2bX9TdeVlsbSOjvezl6zeJqn8/IHJoPkdQ5+oRUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["buys","buy","would buy","will buy"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE24gjl71hT8X4+Owzu39k8vmliV1F6i7Oq1L81Ox8KiaDn8sKgsrcfKZJ6fmleYgyqxWjq3KmA0t6CE0b9DxLFYbryPOuNOIxFr9LZ0sGfV9m8nB8BEGUmlVGl7jiiGs8/1Teymbc8aNjVYbZxo6tEP8dOQRTKpC2te5wUk3oMDo4Prl0DAAtc0ev5MXy5NOjgtz5vPEjB7M6zrJxA45mivFI69pb/1PyKlJRWmBa3Ty4TY5kmZVvfy2rIR0qargYHlOGlA86bH8a4OrQeiOgrdq2iW/RCz47ULzEXGEKinwGvbcqwleHZOMTZU5y1nFPsvdpx3y+wtkoEqXWSUIb1+4InaziAXbwiC047zuw1XVZwy+C9/jcLrCMX49Na3O4s0PxeDfmWm536mNi/Fg25sNX5AboD1MniPW9lsYgzI7lWJa+u8ghrPT1bVbXBwny1CsvGr3ScVo8wES1qPuOvZT6Qo3yxM8DpLBbLVhFa5O/oTPXzy5vPBvPzeFXGIjgQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"21","id":"21049","langCode":"vi","question":"n6zIfQMYL4CW5cP7NqR5KRjUAJbWJfWQOdWWCFeE6v9S5myLsCtyRklufvs/4YnQ","answers":["talk","will talk","has talked","would talk"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE833kNd+5Ct+eEYG76epgLkABS3nfWMJH5+3Ppxr8KsCclSsHAsdkHfUz17iATE7fLXF6rfSx/gPojblr9ZxoGs7m9dODiVgOqeMC9Zmf9crzQ9TTtlOlq7+mwiQnJ/ufFo2ZkSJPY/I6Y+TfA3E77w/dLH1Z8N+QJwgutuwUciv5wNc9xl9AWwH7NmdEevf2kOJYCp44PeSdCZgKTPRQ1+0C4fuMdzay/0c18p0gi/1dgFfvfC88Rn+Q9FmEnvHOgr3AkKLc74FgyPxx0wXpxJQ8XiPSwujvGqa0VoWKXA56uXKBZxF3hEqlmx+IgG0kcSmnc05n456iPzzN125hiy4InaziAXbwiC047zuw1XVZwy+C9/jcLrCMX49Na3O4s0PxeDfmWm536mNi/Fg25sNX5AboD1MniPW9lsYgzI7lWJa+u8ghrPT1bVbXBwny1CsvGr3ScVo8wES1qPuOvZT6Qo3yxM8DpLBbLVhFa5O/oTPXzy5vPBvPzeFXGIjgQ\u003d\u003d"}]